Hello, Hairlessness, welcome back to the tutorial on the cut from the index.
So today we will see the so-called the place that features that directly obtain the futures in the three
dimensional.
Exactly.
We will see today that how to create the holes, standard holes on the three dimensional scales.
And we will see how to make the shell that's useful for the making the bottles, some sand, some sicknesses,
for example, some bottles, some surfaces and so on.
And we will see the how to make the edge blend that all the parameters of that have to make the edge
blend then.
And we will still have to make that the draft.
No, the the not the champion.
We will we have seen the have to make the edge taffer in the Today show.
But in this case we will see in a three dimensional object, then you will see that all the options
of the have to make the draft.
Then we will see here how to make obtain the Venus in the street and out of Threet for the object.
So let's start from the beginning.
Let's select the sketch, select the plan and press, OK?
Throw the rectangle from the center, for example, the new dimension and extruded.
For example.
OK, and select the whole function.
In the hall, we will have the several top of the hall, for example, that's simple, the general home,
the real size home school, Colonial's Home Sweet Home and home series.
We will see all of them step by step.
Let's start with the general hope in the general hold.
We have the several forms of the horse.
There's a simple hold accountable and hold come to thankful and to hold so simple hold.
Firstly, in order to obtain the home, we have to define the specified point of the whole.
We have to define the phase where we want to make the hole.
For example, this phase precede this phase.
And you see there is the the dot is created and you can specify the point of this point by the rapid
dimension.
For example, you can define that position on this point from this and this set, for example, 30 mm.
From this site.
And, for example, uh, 40 millimeters from this side.
We define it the position of the hole and pressed to finish square.
So from this point, the hole is created.
It is the simple hole.
That simple hole.
Let's see from the the side you see it is the simple hole.
And we can define it is the diameter, for example, 15, and we can define it the depth.
For example, it's 16 millimeters.
Or we can define the value of the depth, for example, until the selected until the next or through
body, for example, the physical body can go the school board.
And until the selected tissue selected this phase, it will be called.
Solvability, that's the very end, it will become 50 and a angle.
Is that a hundred is the standard angle for the the the tools that the for the for the drilling tools.
It's the one hand that they can change it.
Yes.
We have to wait for that.
One hundred thirty.
And so in the balloon logic that's always in the hole, we'll get into the supply because we had the
making the hole so.
This is the type of the simple hole if if pressed, OK, you see the hole is created, let's double
click on The Simple Hole.
Let's save you from this side.
And if you change the form of the hole from the simple to countersign, you will not end this kind of
hole.
The value of the counterposed diameter is that this diameter and it should be always the bigger from
the diameter of the dream than from the T side, for example, let's change the values, the let's change
it to the twenty five, for example, and the counter board.
Dempsey said these steps.
Let's change it for the.
Fifteen, and the count of them, at least it's Sternman to 15 and also the deps.
For example, let me be 40 and so on, the also the top angle of this and also we can make the debs,
according to the limit, will use this is a useful authority.
The goal is to subtract Alwis.
She.
Counter bolt hole is created.
And as a form of the whole is thank.
That is the fact is that this bigger diameter and also we have two angles, it's called the sunk angle,
this angle and angle, this angle also the the diameter is this trailing diameter and the depth is 40
also the same that we can define the value according to the limit they lose in this kind of hole.
If you would like to make the the.
See the last about the whole.
Is the table at home this kind of hope so in the time, for example, if it's 20 to being admitted and
the angle, this angle is certainty and the depths, for example, you can make it 60.
And so.
So.
Let me obtain the simple and if you would like to make the hole at the angle, you can make the along
the vector, for example, the change the whole direction, not the normal to fail, but along the vector.
In this case, you can or you can make it by the two points and define the two points.
For example, to this point in this point, you will obtain the whole lot at this point.
Let's make this point.
You will obtain the whole.
In the angle, and if you make the value that the the body, you can obtain the whole in this direction
from starting from this point, at this point also you can make this point or in this point, unless
you want this, sell the security circovirus.
This is the have to obtain the whole forums also.
We have the type of holes, for example, the drill holes.
Let's the.
Think of this one and delete this for.
Open the hole from the type of the hole that make it the drill size hole, this drill hole is and use
it for the milling operations, for the same operations.
If you need it to some drill holes, you have to choose the drill holes directly from the this part.
So in this case, you have also predefined position of the hole from, for example, this phase and
that this hole position is created in place finish.
And hear from the former and I mentioned there is the standard for the drill sizes that the standard
sizes for the drilling operations and can define your required drill size, for example, time and the
depth you can define as you as you previously.
To limit or just to give the volume and then keep angle, but also drill hole is created.
This is the standard holes for the drilling operation during the milling operation.
So.
The same.
The three that holes and screw holes that the kindie obtain it.
Screw holes and then three holes.
And then there is the standard sizes for the straight holes exist in that in the market, for the drilling
operations, for the 3D, in the existing standard values for the 3D.
So in order to see the more serious holes, that whole series, let's do.
Well, one more object.
For example, let's firstly define the Dow tumbling, that tumbling.
At a distance.
For example, that is true, not employees.
And the press, OK, let's throw one thank you for this stop complain.
And extruded, that's enough, and let's throw one.
Rectangle 40 is also.
Extruded also, that's enough and open the whole.
And choose the type of the whole whole series.
And this five point.
And this week.
You see in the whole series, there's the directly the system defines the holes for the consequent objects.
So it's the third object.
This is the middle object and this is the end object.
So the hole is seriously created step by step for all serious objects.
It's too easy.
So it's a simple hole.
And from the start, you can find that the type of the holes and the where that standard values for
the holes and and you can find the depth, the deep angle.
Also, you can define the values and the limited values.
This is how to obtain the whole series.
Well, that the whole series of holes, so this is the all about the how to create the holes and to
continue the with the espeland, for example, the espeland list, we can delete all of this.
And we can delete the place and remain just this.
Rectangle.
For example, in the ESPELAND, if you select Espeland function, you will see two type of the size
of the circle and cornichon.
Firstly you will see the circle espeland if you select the edge, for example, in the airplane, it
will be made around.
That you see is the diameter of 20 millimeters and you can change the values by hand as a drag in dropping
these arrows.
It is the symmetrical change so you can change the value by putting the numbers, for example, the
30 millimeters and so on.
So also in the here.
Here you see the in the, uh, the variable at this point, if you open the variable Redish points and
the selector is five points.
From here, if you make the end point, let's to select end points of this, this one and this one to
end point is selected and that you can change the values of the this and the others and make the variable
at this point.
So all you can put it in the number, for example, 20 millimeters here and from here you can change
the values.
Twenty millimeters, so it is there the same also from here you can.
The.
The point on the edge and the selective dispatch and you can make it in the middle, for example, and
change the middle value, reduce, for example.
To turn, then you see here, you will obtain the various shape of the eligible and.
We see.
That's to make it to change the color in order to be to see the exact effect of the eligible and assign
the future color specified color.
We can see.
Uh, from from this site, for example.
You see here the constant value of the edge of the land.
Constant.
To explain in this side and here we see various well-loved espeland, for example, in the various fell
off the edge of Berlin.
You can hear define the many points, more than three points according our project.
So.
For example, let's delete this part and make to explain the game.
On the Three Corners, for example, let's do this one, and here we have cornered the corner setback
function in the corner, setback function.
If we have three plants in one corner, for example, The Selecter, select and board, select at this
point and we can open this list.
We have three and one, two and three.
And we can define the values of this column called Blancs by hands or just the number.
For example, here we have this value system, for example, gifty and.
This will resemble the 15.
And then this will.
Fifteen and so we can define the difference in the scale we define it, the same numbers of the corners,
the corner blank, and you can define the different values.
For this corner blank, so it is the path to contain the corner.
In the case of the eggplant.
OK, it's clear about Cottenham setback and also we have the function that's the option of the stop
short of the corner.
Let's open the store for protocol.
So specify the point, select and point.
If you select, for example, this end point and then throw you see the you can define the exact position
of the user.
Uh, if you if your blend.
So the press you see here.
You can define by hand you the position of the plant espeland.
So also, we have the treatment option that used to select object by the plane, for example.
Also, we can define the position of the ESPELAND, for example, if you like this edge, you can define
the.
The limit position for the Aspelin also you can change the direction from this site.
All this this is the how about all the function of the functions of the ESPELAND, I think there is
no question about Aspelin pledge to continue with the chaffer function.
We can delete this all.
So let's continue the chaffer in the chancer, if you open the channel for this, the option to select
EDG, she select the edge.
You see, you will obtain the comfort in the two dimensional scale.
But in this case, it is in a three dimensional.
This is the cross section is a symmetric.
It means it is the the same from 1770 milimeter from the both sides.
You can change the value by cutting the numbers for a number 20.
And so on or by the hand, you can change the values.
In the case of the symmetric, it is that in the case of decimeter, you will see the two values from
the two sided issue, for example, dragged into this arrow.
All of these is changing that this one is constant.
All you can change this value in a different way of this one so you can put the number here for them.
Thirty and twenty then.
So in the.
Also, the value offset and angle, you will define that distance.
This is the distance and this is the angle of the chamber, so it is simple about the temple.
I think that's the clear about the chain from below.
So next is about let's continue with the draft.
In the draft, we'll see different values that, for example, from plane or surface, that from the
edge, the tangent to the face to painting to parking it.
So let's start with the foam plane image.
So in the from the plane, you have to first specify the vector or you can define that this face, for
example.
And you can if you have to define the stationary part in phase.
So that's the sixing stationary in that phase.
So this phase.
Sorry.
Specify the vector, this face stationer face and select the face where you want to make the draft.
So, for example, this phase you see it is a 10 degree of the with the draft.
Ten degrees of you can change the values or you can right here, the values, for example, salt and
add new said, and you can make it rough for this new set and you can trust angle for this angle.
And so you can make the different values.
For example, in this side, for example, 20.
And that is drafting a certain distrust and a certain distrust and at least 20 mm.
You see here, 30, 30 and 20 and so on.
And here also you see the draft method that is now we use it, the drafting is the stationary face draft
angle.
So there is also option departing face and stationary in parking first draft.
So we see this, a stationary face drafting.
This face was stationed in Seoul.
Just.
This phrase was station, so open the draft promptly and let's see what is the part you face in order
to make to see the what is the part faithless to draw one.
Skitch.
All this face.
Let's throw the mark.
And let's turn it extruded in the symmetric area and that this.
Playing that should be bigger than this rectangle press.
OK, so we obtain a plane and make the draft the different from plane or face the estimated parking
fees, that vector lets to define this face and select a station in a parking space.
We have to define this plane and select the face in which we would like to make to the draft.
This phase, you see only this part is drafted until the D phase.
So, for example, the new said and this angle.
OK, that's the hardest we see.
This is very important
function to make the draft in the complex shapes.
Also, for example, let's delete this one.
And for example, sketch or.
Cylinder.
Any any damage to so extruded?
For example, in this position and select a sketch and this plan, but it's OK also, for example,
you can draw ARC in this position and extrude it in a symmetric RELU.
That should be a little bit bigger.
Listecki.
Drafts the method of the parking fees.
From the plane interface, select parking, face this face and select the face where I would like to
make the draft this face.
You see all of this part is crafted.
Let's seat.
This is the ultimate method of the draft using the parking space.
This one, it is very useful and I think it's the clear let's delay this.
Skitch.
You draw the rectangle.
Extruded.
OK.
OK, next is the method of drafting is the station in the parking space, it's the making the draft
using the two previous methods.
So in order to do this, let's make the also the additional security that is produced on this plane.
For example, let's say in this case.
The rope line.
Extruded, we're going the cement that really.
OK.
OK, draft.
Stationary in the partial face.
Satisfied the vector, the stationary face in this case, it is this rectangle.
Selected partying face.
No, no, sorry.
This actor.
Uh, in this case, the sole that station in a phase, this phase and the parking and this.
Select a face where we would like to make the draft these fees, for example, and these fees, but
it's OK.
Hide this war and you obtain such kind of trust in this method.
Delete this one.
Okay, open the draft and we'll see other parts of the making the draft, for example, from the edge.
It is very easy.
You have to first define the vector and you have to define the edge in order to make to draft this policy.
Also in the edge, if you opened here, the this one and you have variable traffic points, so if you
define the points, for example, this point in this point or more point in the.
Can by hand that they find very loose here, the drafting of a different variable drafting, for example,
this one.
And for example, like this.
And the specified point, for example, uh, uh, point on the edge, for example, this point, we
can define the different points in the.
Can make the different.
Drafting goes like these by hand, so by putting the number, so it's making the draft Àngel.
Using the from edge and from Lapointe's.
Let's delete and we have also the tanjim to face the tension, to face drafting, to make the drafting
in this case.
Listen to this one.
In this case, for example, in the case of the Times and Faces, if you have the talent in places like
Egypt, for example, like this.
It's meant to be to you.
You cannot do this drafting it like from the plane.
Like this, you cannot do like this, it will be a big mistake.
So in the case of the like the Times and facing the like the ESPELAND, you have to use the Tanjim face
to make the edge plan.
So you have to specify the vector days and select the face of the time.
And so this phase in order to make the order to make the draft, so.
Can make that you can make the draft in the case of the such kind of cases.
This is the last part two part engage, so.
Almost the same of that about the parking fasold specify the vector, the plane.
No, in this case, for example, firstly, we have to split down the bodies in order to split the body,
for example, open the mall and split the body, select the body and select the face that in this case
led to this face, this body.
The final disgrace and OK.
That's to hide this.
So the border is split into two parts, so draft.
To putting it select the vector, this vector, select plane to stationer playing this phase, select
Jesso.
This is so you will make the draft until this political object.
At least.
Like this.
This is the oil sanctions, that's the possibilities of the job to make the draft, so let's delete
this one and.
Next is to make the let's delete this one, this this also lets to see the shell function itself is
needed in order to make the same rules for the solid functions.
Uh, it's very useful to obtain the bottles.
And this is kind of, uh, objects.
So we have to type of the shells that's to remove face and then shell and so all the face.
So let's see, firstly the all face and shell.
So in this case, you have to select, for example, that this face so you will make the shell of the
object on this file that five minutes.
So let's make the 10 millimeter so you can make the shell, for example, select also the displays.
You can make the shell.
That's kind of, uh, solid objects convey to the shell object.
So also, if you see here, the alternative sickness.
So if you select, for example, the D phase, you can do differently, give the value for D well,
for example, that let's make it to 20.
So all the D side is will they come to 20.
Mm.
And others means a 10.
So a new set and we can make for 10 Mm.
Of this site.
So this is the half to make this shell and the.
This is very useful for to making their say mission for the making the bottles, so do it this show
and open the shell and see the shell or the face and select the body selected.
OK, so it will become the initial for the whole of the bodies.
And you can see this by the in the View section.
There you see in the show of 10 millimeter from them, all the sides.
This is the about cell function.
Let's see the last topic of the day about the threat, how to make the inner and outer streets.
Murder to make the sweet list so that the plane and the sketch and.
Slender.
And extruded.
And the open the more sweet we have to type of the trade, that symbolic, sweet and the detail of the
table is very useful to get through to selected these.
And this will define the exact that the values for that this take in the mind of them at length.
OK, lets the.
Define the value for this, for example.
For Honda executive.
Finish it.
And also for the extrudes, let's make it.
700.
And open the street so like this, once you see it, the major damage to the system, which we draw,
therefore the circle for Hundert and it will define the system as it defines a minor, the meter, it's
a three hundred ninety four or so.
We can change this for this.
We want to sample the three hundred ninety and so on that length.
That's the that extruded length and that's the pitch and angles.
So classic.
So we obtain the our street, if you would like, for example, to change the values again, the.
Double click on the street and the change, the values to obtain in the streets for the, uh, for this.
OK, this is the ultimate outer suite, let's see the how to obtain the industry, for example, in
order to meet in the States, you have to select the they have to do the whole.
For example, the this here and the.
Extruded.
In the opposite.
Directions, that's the limits.
And the Dismas make it on Hundert.
And subtract this, OK, so hole is created and open the sweet.
That they selected this face and this is defined it by the system.
And for example, the press took.
For example, Alice.
OK, let's make it more bigger.
The.
Okay, let's to draw another.
Object, so delete this one, delete Android sketch.
OK, so that this phrase.
So, for example, linehaul extruded.
Subtract the sick and the sweet.
That they let's treat.
So this will select the starting point.
This won't look OK, so we've seen the in the 3D cleated.
And the you see here is.
In this thread, so dear students, let's this all about of today's lesson that we have seen how to
create holes.
So the draft energy plan that Camford and Threet in and out to.
This is the topic of the place that features that existing polluted futures for the three dimensional
subject.
See you in the next lessons.