All of this will come back to on the cut from the next day, we will see the pattern features the several
type of pattern that you just have to make, the pattern, the features, that's the circular pattern,
linear pattern, polygon spiral.
And along the guide temperatures as well as today.
Also, you'll see the middle of the features to mirror of the features along the surface along the that
in place.
So far we have seen the mirroring of the sketch, two dimensional sketch in this sketch, the glasses,
and in this case you see the middle of the three dimensional features.
So let's start with the pattern of the features.
So in order to do this, let's throw one simple.
Kids so select a rectangle from the center.
OK, the mission is not.
OK, let's extend it.
So we can sketch again, selected to face this wicked.
Draw one more rectangle using the two points.
OK.
And extruded.
So.
Then make the drafting go.
By three.
OK, so.
The.
We prepared our base case, so I would like to make the extrude of this element along the base axis
and this axis, so in order to do this, open the letter in the future, he you see that there is several
options off to make the layout them.
You just as I mentioned before, that it's the linear circular polygon spin along the helix.
So we will see all of them as examples, example, step by step.
Let's start with the linear, so linear layout.
So in the selected future, you will select a this feature that you would like to make the patterns
of this select.
And you see here the direction in the specify the vector, you can specify the vector, for example,
this direction x axis or ends of the base element.
This does not matter.
So select, for example, this axis.
So you see here the direction of the pattern along the this side, or you can drag and drop on this
side.
So we choose to order that -- of the pattern.
So.
In this case, so here you see that there is the county that represents the number of.
That term, the future, so it is true that to make it fall under that list you see there is the for.
It means that we have four.
That term, the civil war for that in the future.
This week, she did that the future is created along the peace axis for that.
And if the just if you double click the button feature and see here the symmetric, really, if you
click the sematic, really along the peace side will be a period.
Also the three.
In the total for.
Uh, in the future, but in this case, for us, it's not necessary.
So to close this one.
Also, you can make the pattern feature along the this axis.
Using the direction to.
Activate the direction to throw in the if you activate the direction to you.
You can also you have to select the second direction that as a vector, you can select the second direction,
this axis or the edge of the dish.
So select the for example.
You see, the second pattern of future is created along the this axis, and we can make to hold the
count more than a distance, let's make it distance 20 this distance.
So you see the pattern, the future.
This created press, OK?
Just is created in this case along the two direction, so let's open again, but then future also we
can make the symmetric along the second direction by taking this.
Senator Graham saw the destruction of the Middle East created that it is not necessary for us not just
to close it.
You can, uh, in the pattern feature all the patterns that you can increase, the value that incremental
values along the way, along with Xs and OS X is so incremental value is in the in the in the distance
or in the in the drafting.
Let's see this auction.
So here we have the pattern.
Let's open the spectrum in and let's open this.
The bottom so precious and in here in the environment, we have to object, so pattern and exclude in
the pattern, we have shown the balance of comparison.
One indirection to and extrude, we have the limit, stop, limit and angle.
So if you like to make the change, the end limits, just the select and limit, then you have to action
along the action one and along the action to the first speed along the direction wants to add and limit
to the direction.
It is entered and you can put the increment of value, for example, to you can put negative value in
order to decrease in this case and increasing the incremental value of the future along the direction
of.
And let's see what will change.
You see, incremental value of Dillings is increasing by two millimeters along that this X is so also
you can't increase the incremental value.
Along the second direction, just select the end limit and add to the second direction and can put to
rest.
You can.
Incremental value is increasing step by step along the second direction.
So also we can make incremental value increase or decrease in the case of the.
Draftable, for example, the selective draft angle and add to the direction one can put it two or three,
for example, it is increases incremental drafting on the first third actually.
So it is so.
Increasing in this case, it is the drafting.
So it is increasing.
Mr. Richard.
And the encouragement of violence and the little increment of the loose end to the previous position.
Also, in the future, we can individually change the values position in the rotation of the pattern
of futures using the instant point function.
So using that, this also is some point function.
So select this one and we can, for example, select this right click and we can delete our element.
For example, delete and press, OK?
It will be deleted, so individual, the only just one pattern is computer.
So in order to come back to the previous position, just select the standpoint and select this one right.
Click and it will.
Uh, will be shown again so we can do such kind of things.
Also, for example, again, open the instant point.
You can right click and suppress, that will be hidden.
From our so it's not deleted just by just heatin.
Again, at some point.
Um.
Unsuppressed, so to be here again.
Also, we can make the.
Change the position and a lot of X and Y axis will up a lot of this and this X is change that as you
see just change.
But will front end before it was zero and zero.
Also, you can change it in the negative direction.
So it's minus 11 under, for example, minus 11 direction to the socket to change by hand to the position.
Not to make the.
Unless you make the look, it will close to the initial position.
So.
Also, you can make the.
Change the rotation using the user, define it, change the rotation.
This was not let's see.
Rotations change.
Let's turn to the previous position in the last in the can makes this further variance or individual
change, the extrude values like the end limit and the drafting of the individual, change the terms,
for example, and value add and value, and, for example, extend values to turn to mine.
And I would like to change it for T, for example, to see what happens.
So just all only one which I selected, but then she keeps changing it and limit is 40.
So you can like this to change the old individual values like draft in England and limit all the features.
So, again, presto, futures.
And The Selecter, instant value.
Want to make it?
They moved the variance, so just change in the initial position.
So that's all about the pattern of futures in along the.
So let's see the example that Silkroad potentially just in order to do this, let's delete all of this
and select a sketch.
So let the plane that's OK and draw the circle.
OK, extruded.
Rezac, also against Cage, this, explain this.
OK, so draw that circle.
Also, I would like to remain that you can make the pattern of the future not only the extruded features,
but also the holes, all the features you can do to make the hole along the the subtract this would
give.
So I would like to make the root of this whole along the circle of direction so selective that don't
feature.
So selected to hold also you can select the home from the ribbon that from the tree.
So this home, so the layout is a circular specified vector.
Is this vector so directional on this and specify the point is the center point zero zero zero.
OK, so you see the pattern is created that you can see the values.
So, yeah, here we have the spacing's the several sites of the space account and pinche and counterspell
issues, select, count and spam, um, you can your six all the lanes, for example, six 360, so
that all of the features will be.
Located along the border, the circumference of the circle, so is you right here, one hundred eighteen.
It will be just half and the current 12 represents the number of dead, but then the few just 12 numbers
are right here again.
Three hundred sixty they will locate along the angle of the 360 and spacing will be a certain degree.
So also you can see from here, if you like, if you select count and each so spacing is the council
to.
So.
But it's OK that one of the holes is created that's open again.
Also, there is one more useful tool here.
It's called Radiate.
If you activate the radiate, it creates the concentric members.
So you see concentric members is created so you can change the direction.
The concentric member, so it can be outer or inner.
So the same number of the holes and that there is also the pitch distance, the distance between this
and this.
So it can increase or decrease the number of the counts, for example, the three till becomes three.
And so let's make two.
So concentric members is created on the destruction.
Open again.
OK, let's try to activate the concentric members the same as Bruce as a linear pattern.
We have the incremental we can make increment level also in some points in the window, change the values,
which is the same what I have shown, the linear bottom techniques.
So.
That's all about.
Circular layout, it's easy.
So this next is the polygon layout, so in the polling layout, the same, you have to select the features
that you'd like to make them better.
So in the case of political, you have to specify the vector as a linear and not limited circular.
So and specify the point is the center.
Zero zero point.
OK.
So the layout of the pattern is created in a number of sites.
Six is a number of the sites of the polygon.
You can make it eight.
And so on, and the count is four, it is that for every side of the polygon, there is this phone number
of the future one, two, three, four and so on.
Eight numbers in each each number.
This is for number of.
But then you can you can change it, for example, three.
It will be cancer, one, two, three, and so.
You see how it is the updated polygon pattern feature on the button, the same as the circular layout,
we have had it so concentric members along this side will decide it does not matter to us or to.
So it's a little bit intersection because the holes are big, a little bit.
The same as proof we have the pattern increment individually just to increase or decrease the and then
the start limit assaults also, and we do change the position that in some point in the middle change
positions and others like the.
And so.
The same.
Was so.
Let's delete the pattern of the polygon first and also this and this sketch.
Not surprising, but you might make.
Next is this weather pattern, so open the pattern future, select the future that you would like to
pattern layout this bureau.
Who can satisfy the plain normal that you have to specify that this sort of clean.
On the reference vector, you have to stay on that plane, you see this ground is created and from here
you can increase the decrease the loss of the speed.
So you can read the whole picture can make more Smolensky.
Spratleys created.
It is the also that seems to be the case of the pattern in common that increased the length to the limits
and so on, so so the individual, the change operation or individual to change the values and also
the same as the others.
But then she just.
That's Chris.
Also this, in order to go with the better futures type of along, let's draw one simple example sketch
playing hooky.
Draw the line, convert it to the reference and make it offset.
Symmetrical said.
But that's OK.
The.
OK, make it also said.
Not the symmetric.
OK.
And extruded.
OK, so.
Select the select approaches for.
Using the project called.
Let's select the single cause.
So, look, this is.
Kim.
And Mike also said again.
This was.
In the distance of five millimeter.
OK, and throw one circle, for example, here, the damage can to five finish.
So in this case, I would like to make the pattern of that this.
Let's firstly make the whole.
The select a single cause, this one the opposite direction.
Drugs, okay, I would like to make the pattern of the disco along the this line, and so in order to
do this, let's open the pattern, the future, select the method of the.
A long selected future that I would like to make the lets the cement from the desert this future you
see it selected and the.
Select the best, disperse, and let's make it Mammadov to count to 10.
And the.
Beach distances, let's make it the.
Pattern is created and press lets the hard.
This one.
You see, the pattern is created along the line, one more thing that you would like to add, for example,
that it's planned like this on the reference hole, for example, make only the deceased will be added
to the reference one end, if you like to make the pattern of that is one.
That is the two options.
Let's see the first one, for example, the open, the pattern, the future.
And upon the level there is the reference.
So to select the future, that you have to select this one, this one.
So and the to select the pattern, you have to select all the petals that all the issues that are selected
and select the best instant handle.
You have to select the these DOT reference point.
So did the reference board is selected this, this or this, you should have select so this.
Let's check it one more time.
Can, but on future.
OK, to select the circle and place, OK, so this.
But the second way is less so and so the second way and in this, it is just a simple event.
In this case you have to drag and drop the espeland above the pattern, the future.
You see this the drag and Robert will press the button future and select the features you have to into
at the ESPELAND.
You see it, and in the method, it should be very rational, so not to see if it will be simple, it
will not be it can be operator.
So it should you should check its variation and for just to see if it will be OK.
David.
It is applicable for all kinds of the potential, just even before the circle of Lehman and others.
So let's delete.
This all.
I would like to show to have to attend the headlocks pattern in order to do this, let's throw down
the slender.
That's OK, let's throw one future on the surface of the SALENA.
OK, let's make small.
And open the Tetum Future Selecter.
Alex.
Selecta future.
The vector along the Delta axis specify.
The point is a center point zero zero.
OK, you see the helixes created.
You can increase the number of the cones, for example, the 15.
Or you can make ten lists and we can increase the angle, then it will they will become more rounded.
So you see the Alix's created.
This is the method of making the patterns, you just all the types.
So.
Let's delete all of them.
Now is the time to make that learn about the myriad of the future.
So in order to do this, let's draw the one simple sketch.
It should be mirroring the systems, should be the.
Symmetric.
In order to correctly obtain the mirrored object.
And the strudels of this one.
There's enough so and to draw one more element, for example, the.
On this face, the closer to rectangular using the profile function.
OK, extruded also on this direction, the distance is that 10.
So I would like to make the middle of this rectangle along the peace lane on this position so, uh,
I will not draw the rectangle, just make the middle or the more middle the feature that select the
future.
That's the future that I, uh, that I would like to make this future.
So, OK, you can make the existing use existing plan to make the murals all control of the new and
unless, uh, for the first time just use the existing select to clean the display.
You see, the police unit can.
So it is a very easy.
So, for example, if you have the whole.
You can also make a meal of the whole future's.
Then you have to hold I would like to make them build this home on disposition so openly gay in the
near future, select the whole let's select from this spot.
Select existing clean.
This plane you see on the screen that also you can make the middle of the futures objects from the using
the new plane.
Let's see this example on future.
Selected this home, for example.
And you can select a new plane and Rodney Crowell, for example, using those methods, which either
explain it in the previous lesson, for example, at a distance, at a distance from this site, for
example, and ponder this plane, for example, it's just an example and class.
OK, so the hole is created.
Can.
Using the existing in the new place to meet the softer making mural of the future.
OK, so that's all about after today's lesson, and I think that everything is clear then this.
See you on the next lesson.