Hello of welcome, but to do that from the cut in today, we'll talk about the top in the new film.
OK.
Today, we will talk the use of several functions, like the for example, the repulsion and.
Trustability also, we will talk today about U.S. Open Dominion, the insert designed design feature
that is exists existing group, and we'll see the several three parts of the rectangular U shaped in
the cylindrical group.
Will see the three types of the group that's to start with the three.
So that's the draw.
The one huge military do understand.
So select the plane.
OK, and the.
The road for the film directing the animation extruded.
OK, and for example, the selective sketch displays like.
And for example, also, again, the one rectangular example, this position.
And they excluded.
The mostly the group is not the group, the group is needed in order to the strings, the structure,
this same, the structure in the making, the support system that uses their functions and the skills.
So, for example, I would like to make here the rectangle, not directing the triangle.
And in order to do this for the show like this huge and the selected plan where you want to make the
leap and display and that OK.
And from here and select intersection, cool and select this rectangle.
So.
And this central line will be the EPA, this is required in order to create reports of the additional
volume.
So and open the more that's the finish to open, the more.
Open the.
In the selectable, you have to select a whole future body and select the course, you have to select
the new you see the other two types of the types of the the you have to create.
You can create the walls.
So you're going to go to the section in the parallel to the section and you'll see that step by step
to all this kind of the the two oldest kind of Ripsaw in the selected just to select this.
And in this case, you have to sell it to political to the second plane.
And the selecta, you just.
And select the plane just in this case, you have to select the plane that you want to make to grow
this plane and draw the line here with a line, and you can define the extreme values of your group
rape, for example.
Let's make it 10.
And the.
And since.
And change the rules that the pedal to the action plan, so you will create the leap like this, you
see you can drag and to increase the wall so you can hear the symmetric more 20.
So you will obtain the such kind of freep.
In order to support this.
This war, so it's the one method of the to create that for the earth, for the rectangle.
Fut..
For example, if you would like to make the leap in this kind of sketch from the edge to edge, it is
the same that it will be not the problem.
For example, let's see this example, escalate this one and open the grip again and select the plane
to where you want to make the leap.
That display, for example, and press and the sketch, the line from the edge to edge, from the edge
to the edge.
So end up press the finish.
So that add up to deception plan is activated and that you see here the edge that is created from the
edge to edge.
There is not any difference between the previous example.
So this is the how to create the rip on the sofa and the rectangular feature.
So let's see the different side of the leaves for the for example, in the circular cylinder.
So that's really this one.
And this also and this sketch also lets the select a sketch and the selected this face a
rectangle, not a rectangle.
The circle.
Throw the whole circle extruded.
Extruded and Rezac, in this case, to drop the rape, also the same, we have to force the sketch obtained
intersection code so the display
and the intersection curve on the cylinder.
On this side, for example, I would like to make a trip to the intersection confiscated.
Now let's open to the beginning from the let's let's finish this sketch and more open drib and select
the body.
The whole body selected and selected could firstly, you have to select the plane that the middle plane
that you want to make this plane and this OK.
And the same is true.
For example, the line in this case, the first case, that line with from the note etched into it like
this and the same as the previous, again, defined the distance from here to here.
And for example, the 10 and the same question here, what does that suggest?
Example, the numbers.
So and finish the sketch.
The rebels created as a parallel to the section point, the method and similar to commute 20 minutes.
So you see here the music takes the shape of the cylinder here and it takes the shape of the rectangle
straight line from here.
So it do hard to obtain the right, but have to obtain that evidence.
This is the same as the rectangle one.
Almost the same.
In the case of the cylinder, if you would like to have the dream acting and the triangle leap from
the edge to edge, it will be a little bit different.
And I will show now how to obtain the grip on this kind of looked at and then this kind of cylinder
from edge to edge.
In this case, we have to use the V or the sweat.
You will not learn this motion so far, but in upcoming the lesson you learn this a fashion.
Now just I will show you how to obtain the Reep with slope function.
So first this and this one in order to do the.
Let's throw the.
Uh, reference.
So this is OK.
That's led to make the project crews using this, the edge of this, the top edge of the cylinder edge.
That's OK then.
Draw the line here.
Also, an additional line here to equal length, then make them symmetric.
On the x axis and let this define the distance between them, the distance between these two lines,
the treacherous for the DVDs of the book, if I will make the 10 or so we thought to review the 10 millimeter,
then using the Greek team flashin.
Just delayed this part of the circle and convert that to the reference to the reference in the press
definition.
The same thing lets to do the same thing, that on the bottom part of the resealing, the sketch look.
You.
Make it a project called.
This part.
OK.
And that.
And the.
Two lines, the same line this.
One.
And make them sematic.
Less to define the distance first, the.
And the make it them sematic, I hope it works.
And convert them to the reference line.
And quick to that part of the Silko
sketch.
OK, one more thing, the sketch.
This face this week, the same thing, that little.
And Rick Stengel, this project could have this edge.
Drawing the line here.
Makes them.
And define the distance between the two lines.
Then.
And convert them to the reference line to lines and three moved to these two sites.
That's one of the first lines created in order to obtain the leap from the edge to edge.
Again, one switch to like the middle plain where you want to do the leap.
OK, now the be careful to draw the district and you have to select the exact points, the intersection
points of the.
The lines.
Then.
Connect this.
This point.
And finish.
So.
It is created to open the surface, then swept.
On the selective growth.
You have to select this rectangle.
And select across the list of more.
Again, once again, firstly, that you have to select the guide, so let's select the guides so we
select these three guides that go the first line, so select this one.
A new said.
Like this one, a new set.
And select this one.
Bad news that.
And.
Smoothness.
I like to call this.
So is a new set and this.
For the Sillett.
That means select the cause, you have to select this rectangle.
And this one and this one, so you see rabies treated in the case of the circus, in the case of the
cylinder from the edge to edge.
So with the traditional last produces is a rectangle.
It's not possible to obtain the leap from the edge to edge.
So it is the view of in India and.
In the Solyndra case.
With the comment of the swap and upcoming lessons will be we to learn deeply about the step function
to obtain some complex two-faced.
And then so.
Okay, so just, uh, let's see the kind of thing there, it's not the rectangular lips, but they're
a little bit too complex.
Rape's also the scene of the hospital in parallel to Section Plenderleith.
So that's the first deleted this all of the projects.
With the oldest kids.
Also, this, uh, this one also know you can continue to do so, and that's for the excluded the higher
ed and let's make it show.
Opportunites make the upper part shell and press.
So who made the show?
We only know how to make the show that we would learn.
For example, the.
That's the.
That plane selected that plane at that distance, for example, from this did make the plane from this
distance in the distance, let's make it like this, but OK.
And the left to draw one sketch on this cartoon play sketch.
They start to plan in press.
OK, so.
That's the sketch.
The.
That's kind of.
OK.
And make.
Geometrical strains of first of to make it the horizontal and make the tangent this line.
We did this line, so finish the sketch.
It's not only.
Mr. Cedar.
It is not on the plane, let's delete this one.
I said that the different planes of.
They start to blame this, they created Ricky.
Well, the arc here.
And that's the.
Ryan, and let's make it.
You.
That make it to an urgent.
And finish the sketch, so you see the line is created on the dot plane created that plane.
So open the Reep function.
The selectable the body selected and selected because this could you see this scandal freebees create
you can change the direction like this.
And you can decrease the value.
You see, the rebels create using the parallel to the section plane, so it is the parallel to the action
plan.
Also, you can create that perpendicular to the plane.
So it will be the dissection plane.
Is the airplane the color to the section, you can change direction.
So these are the two way of delfine.
And rape in the city, kind of this kind of mentality can make the perpendicular to the sexual plain
so that of the river is perpendicular.
And this is the parallel to the section plate.
And you can hear the make the symmetric graylin and asymmetric Valen.
So the sickness and open here and there is the cab.
That's all said.
You can make it from the section this to you can make it all sit on top of this all said the detail,
you can increase the offset value by hand or just divide it up a little steam.
This is the from the section plan.
It means that the document plane.
So from the docking in place, it increases also the 15 millimeters, the above.
Also, you can add the draft angle.
You see the draft angle, for example, let it be the size.
And let's preview from the top side.
You see the draft angle and that five degrees.
She's the only method of building in the complex groups, so let's delay this rip and the to complain.
Yes, let's remember that blame and less do one.
And that's the.
Let's decide first that this complaint and this bottom face.
OK, well, that's the little one.
Cylinder here, for example.
And
extruded.
Excluded and less, the game show the to playing here and Skitch.
These are totally OK, let's do the sketch one.
Spline line.
You can play is the relevance of the supply line like this, but this week, let's convert this blind
line into a rip.
Finnish.
So like the of this good.
You see, the read is created along the spline line can increase or decrease the value or just like
the exact value here.
Also, we can make that different trip like this on that side or on this side, the using the reposts
that have been parallel to the U.S. plane or LEAP.
Perpendicular to the U.S. plane like this.
So also, one more thing here in the geometry, in the cap, you see there is the from the section in
the section, it means that the from the from the bottom and from there you hear the from the selected.
Also you can select from the selected.
It means that the selected existing face, for example, this of the cylinder you can select the face
and you see it.
Grossed.
Like this issue, for example, did like this and increase, for example, the value here, you see.
It will go up from the surface or it should make like this only goes.
That's the new.
This one.
Kept from the selected.
So.
Can select us a limit, the value of the surface of the space and any surface, in this case, the surface
of the cylinder.
Again, this is a mess to put to offset from the surface, for example, the six, so it goes up from
the surface of the six millimetre from the surface of the cylinder.
OK, that's all all about options, possibilities and techniques of the leap.
And let's go on the other side.
Today's futures.
OK, next list, I mentioned this group list for all the projects related to rape.
So sketch that to draw the one cylinder before the study, the group.
So.
OK, finish sketch and extruded.
That make it all you.
OK.
Open the menu.
Insert design features and here you see the group and there is the three types of the you can obtain
the rectangle bowl and then you could have led to see that all of them stand best unless the first left
from the rectangle select a rectangle and select the face where you want to obtain the groomed face
of the cylinder.
So there they exist.
There will be developed.
You will obtain the dimensions of the grill.
This is the grill diameter is the inner diameter.
So this is the width of the group.
Let's change this.
For example, the as you also to stone and let's I mean this and if you'd like to define the correct
position.
Okay.
So the group is initiating.
So if you would like to the put the current position for a group, you have to select this edge and
this edge.
You will see that the distance between the this HMD it and the you can exactly right.
The any number for example.
Thirty five and plus.
You see, the group is created, it's a rectangle group.
You see the depart, this rectangle here, the 040 scope rectangle grew.
Take it and let's see the ball and groom.
Also, you have to select a face where you want to make the group.
So this is face and the groom.
Diameter is 37, so it represents the diameter smaller.
So let's make it the more vigorous.
Make maybe 50 folds less.
OK.
So.
The same define that they can define distance by the clicking this edge and this edge.
So let's make it 90, OK?
You see?
The bull and group sold some.
Born and grooves created is the diameter of the 50.
It was before the rectangle rectangle grew was so missing the.
So take it.
Last time you said you grew the same, you have to select the face selected, so in this case you will
select group diameter, the Elseworlds of these fits, the C and the group radius, it lets them all
of them the same K, the same as previous to so let's say like this one and this one to select the distance
position, 150 less.
OK.
You see, the you grew U.
U.
Shaped groups created with the diameter is 50 and the width of 13, and here the radius is two point
five.
So this is the optimal group.
So it is the three types of groups and it is the outer group.
You can also make the entire group.
So in order to make the list, select the sketch.
Sketched this face this week, let's draw the whole here.
With the diameter of steel and extruded.
When they won the election and subtract this, OK?
So let's make it's the distance.
Smolla.
So let's draw the group, this group or this.
So again.
Meenu.
Insert designed futures.
And open the group, so let's start directing a little so select selective phase where you want to make
in this case is in this phase and it's good to see 50.
So it is the diameter of the hole.
And it is this is the sort of press.
OK, so it's great.
And if you would like to define the.
Position.
You have to select the edge, and here you cannot find the edge of the group.
So in this case, you can hear the static wireframe frame and select this test line in order to see
in order to see the distance itself.
So let's make it sort the exact numbers.
This week.
So.
To see that's.
And.
OK, this one.
And the right frame.
To.
This one.
You have to in this case, to increase the weather, for example, his 12 and.
See, the group is created, most of these see the U.
S..
You see in a group, he's created so little damage that shouldn't be the bigger the diameter.
So in this case, you will obtain the.
Inter-Group.
This group, --, should be this was 50 and it should be bigger than the.
In them, it get to them.
So let's see one more game.
The insert designed future.
You, for example, you grew.
The face, and it should be twice correct this week and less to define the distance, for example,
from this edge and like.
From the time this distance is let's make it 50.
OK, let's shift shifted.
And let's see this result you section.
So since this al Qaeda group is created in their group is created, this is the method of obtaining
seatbacks of the group.
So.
I think there is no question about tomorrow, it's easy enough to define the position and define the
inner and outer groups, this it will tell.
And the last of today's topic is the draft board as to the role the.
Selena.
Smallness, I mean, the.
Not like this and about the draft, we have the loan and we will today loan the draft board, it's almost
the same, but there is also some differences.
And let's to make this sketch again, not the case, but the plane that the plane of the method of the
dissector, it's the middle of the two.
He says so in the meeting this week.
So in this case, the open the draft here, you see the draft from the original draft phases to the
draft from the age and from the Sunnis, from the age and from the here.
You will select the pathing object, so in this case, it is this selection and the will select created
a select age above the party.
So this age and select age level of the party.
This age.
So and.
You select the vector, this vector.
And so you make the draft submitted a draft of this cylinder.
Also.
You can make the draft.
For example, the change the.
Party object on this site and personal key will be drafted along this along the length eight of the
cylinder.
This is the how to obtain the draft and it is easy.
That's all for today.
See you on the next list.