Hello, Soudas.
Welcome back to the tutorial from the.
Today, we will see the.
Right.
The lesson on the design features that the features needed in order to obtain the direct 3-D model objects
without using the sketch.
And extrude functions just directly obtained several Shapard featured elements like that could be called
ComicCon Sverre and so on, and also several whole elements.
So in order to remove the token, the design features, let's open the menu and there is the insert
and here you see the design features.
Up to now, we learn the design features like the extrude the wolf.
We learn the whole.
And on the whole, the crew and the rip and sweet and today that we will learn how to obtain the direct
looked the lenders to cause fear and the pocket pad and the slot.
Uh, well, this kind of element.
So let's see the let's see from the block.
So the block here you see the three options to obtain the block by the origin, by the two points and
by the two points, the two points of the diagonal.
So let's see that by the origin.
So in this case, you have to specify the point where you want to obtain your two blocks.
So in this case, let's select the origin.
And here you see that it's given the different dimensions of the log.
It's the length, width, and you can change the values as you want.
For example, let's make it one hundred fifty.
The DVDs is the one hundred and OK, so this is enough.
You can see the log is created directly not to use the scales and extrude function.
You can the.
Exactly.
They obtained a block from the set from the system.
So this is the one method of obtaining the bloke using the whole point from the origin.
Let's the this one and open agenda.
Ballock.
The.
By two points and hate the first point to specify the point it represents for us the origin point,
this point and the specified second point represent for us the heat of the.
Heat of the moment, you can make it by the in the numbers here or just to the point, for example,
like this and Prestwick and the you can define the heat here.
Just head around that direction, and in this case, it's 100 like it and it lets you see the block
is created by two points and one eight.
Can delete.
This one and open again, the design features the ballock, and the next step is two points and two
points in the dirt with the two with the dagger.
So of this method, so Spitfire pointed to the origin this point and specified the point is a diagonal
position.
Let's define it like putting the values specific values.
One hundred, for example, round the x axis.
Let's make one hand around the Y axis and just takes let's make the 150 on the hate that axis.
So the point is created and the press, where can we see this point and this point using the two points,
the different side of the of the block is created.
That's the down and let's see, you know, the shape to create.
Is the cylinder on the cylinder, we can create a cylinder, right, traumatised by the axle, by the
using the arc.
Let's see the first about the axis, the specify the vector, which means that you have to specify that
the vector for the heat of the cylinder or it came to this axis or this axis the same or desexualized
see two sections.
First, this exercise selected as a vector and specify the point of origin.
And here you see the dimensions of the cylinder is the diameter.
And here you can change the world as you want.
So let's say, OK, so since the direction of X is more selective, that axis so that the the cylinder
head is, uh, on the debt on that.
So let's see the different way of creating the cylinder.
Design the future.
Surrender and let's select a specified vector them in this case, the data exists, for example, then
remained dimensions of the southern end of the sea.
And in this case, you see the we selected the direction of the cylinder on the tracks.
And so that's why the cylinder is laying on the bed axis.
So let's it.
This one and let's to see the crate cylinder is the ark in order to do this, let's get the ark mostly,
OK?
Lists a broad arc.
Let's put the.
They the show for it more than 100, yes, OK.
Finish the scourged, so Arkes created let's to open the design feature.
And the method of the cylinder and from here from the Tablas Select Archim he so select the arc of this
arc, so this is the direction of the little bit at the direction of the cylinder.
So the heat is left one hand and so you see the cylinder is created and in this case the diameter of
the.
The diameter of the cylinder will be to the diameter of the arc.
It is 100.
So let's it this all.
Let's see the another design feature.
It is the cone, this several of the creating cause.
Let's see all the warmest enough to do understand what is the console selected this one specified vector.
You have to specify the direction of the cone.
So in this way, to specify the point is the origin of the so called start.
And there is the dimensions of the college, the base diameter.
It's the top diameter, in this case zero.
And the heat is 25.
So let's make it bigger cone.
Let's make it one hundred and let's make it 50.
OK, so you see the cone is created also.
You can change the top diameter, for example, the 20.
And it will be become the 20 millimetres of the diameter in the top of the cone did stitches the method
of the heart to create the cone, so.
It's the deleted outtake inserts designed for children last year, so it is the two methods of tale
of the severe weather center point in diameter and by the artlessly, the first one.
So beside the point, as usual, you have to specify the center point.
So in this case, you can select, for example, the origin point and here you see the diameter of the
your sphere.
So it certainly lets the press okay in order to obtain the sphere.
So sphere the diameter of 30 millimeter on the origin point is created.
So this is the hub to obtain directly the sphere.
Press the delete.
So next to the top 10 in the series by the arc, so same as the underground theme of the arc.
Well, the beginning.
OK, you can define the tone of the.
The radius of the article, let's make it 50.
Finish the sketch artist created, then open the.
Design the future select this year.
So from here, the select the ARC special in here, select art.
You have to select the sketched art and just press.
So art is created so that the sphere is created and it is the.
It is the diameter is 50 millimeters to the meter of the arc.
So this is the day to the day that features from the design feature commitment not to use the sketch
techniques and extra techniques.
OK, Susan, so that's how about the hospital plane that direct fut. so left this fear, this Arkansas
McCalister firstly the design feature and we have seen this for design feature now to see that the such
kind of design features like the Boss Pocket Pad and Slok, we have seen in the previous
lectures the plane grew up and the whole staff to see it.
These are the four elements.
So in order to obtain the slides to make the first to create the book.
So by the.
Or religion near this point for the police to make the lengths on hand the let's make it with safety
and hate, let me 20 less.
OK, so block is created.
On the design feature.
First is the boss.
Is the.
The like, the cylinder.
You can read directly the Swindell the cylinders feature so you can define the diameter, for example,
the 20 millimeter, the heat and the temporal angle.
So let's make firstly the.
They're putting a zero unless the selective where you want to make the Boasso on this face, so you
see.
The the wealth is created, the Hato 30 millimeter and the diameter of the limit.
For example, if you like to make the Tepfer angle like previous five.
It will become the draft engeleiter draft, so, OK.
You see the canisters, the drafting, and if you would like to make that define the position of these
goals, you have to use the these horizontal vertical in this dimension, for example, the horizontal
dimension.
You have to select the edge.
And to this, it defined the horizontal from the.
So we should like to make it the middle you right here, the value and the length was one hundred.
Let's make it 50 to bring it in the middle.
That's OK.
And it will become still in the middle of the land.
So in this case, for example, if you would like to change the values, for example, in the position
in the pyramid, let's make firstly the positions.
So a determination in that direction.
For example, this point.
On this point, our accent so ill defined at this point as it was, the 50 or so in this case will be
25 Listecki.
Gail.
So.
The this was located on the middle of the.
In the middle of the rectangle, so to the how to locate it, and you should like to change the balance
of the balls, you can right click and here the added parameters and future dialogue so you can change
the values.
For example, they can change the heat for 40, for example.
And the time to listen to the 30 Rock and see it is the change of decisions of today in the.
The both.
So you can.
Need to disperse and go to the desired future.
Next is the type of the desired future is to see the pocket, so you see there is the title of the pocket
you can make the cylindrical and rectangular, thin, little cylindrical selecta, cylindrical select
face.
And you see that the the the the the dimensions of the pocket disappear.
So you can write the specific values for the dimensions that the pocket diameter, that it's a cylindrical
pocket.
So that circular pocket depth.
And so we will certainly create what you see.
It's located here and you can define the specific positions that clicking the position this.
And this.
This one and the center park, so it's 25.
Let me take it from the position of the 50 in the middle and on this direction, let's make it.
Let's make it the middle 25.
OK, so it is located in the middle pocket, cylindrical pocket.
So if you'd like to change, for example, the parameters or indeed the parameters for future dialogue,
here you see the floor, the radius, Shumake, the floor is, for example, the two real.
Quoting here, to reduce or can you see is a two millimeters lower.
Also, we can make it as a taper angle here.
Let's make it.
Sorry.
OK.
It's the taper angle.
You can see the Camp Tapert angle, the three degrees, so.
This is the how about the cylindrical pocket?
Let's do with this and see how to paint a rectangle pocket insert design feature.
Pocket, in this case, a rectangle pocket, and select the phase where you want to obtain the pocket
and the solid face in this face, you see here real.
Obtain the parameters for the rectangle packet that lends itself to limit the reach of 20 million deaths,
10 millimeters less to remain the size of zero.
We will see later.
Okay, so you see the rectangle pocket is created that's located to press the horizontal dimension and
press this one.
And this will let you see that you can define the position.
Let's make it.
50.
That's OK.
And the vertical direction like this one and this one make it twenty five on the middle.
So can we can you see it is located in the middle of the rectangle.
So let's see other parameters of the rectangle pocket, the parameters.
Future I look you see here, the corner there is the corner there.
This is the 3D Paradis.
So this Paradiso hello radiuses to this floor.
Let's make it, for example, Conelrad two.
And that is true.
And there is also just a taper angle as a producer also.
So let's first.
Okay.
You can see it will become the reddish.
Two millimeters called Marantis and the flow rate is well, so you can add, uh.
Tapering, well, okay, let's delete all of them.
And open the then future, so we have seen the polls that let us see the path.
So you see here that you will obtain the pad of rectangle pad, so select the face as usual.
So let's face this face.
You see here you will see the values of the rectangle.
Petzold language and hate list remain the zero other parameters to the rectangle that is created the
same of the location on the horizontal selector.
The value.
And this will you will see that the direction from this side is nine point three, let's make it.
Fifty on the middle class, OK, and vertical direction from this side to this side, so let's make
it.
Uh.
Let's remain to the same interests.
OK?
So.
It is located here and also the design parameters feature dialogue you will see here in the corner.
Let's make it to impress or to see decordova.
This is become the field of two redish two degrees.
So this is a top 10 rectangle.
So this one also the other corner, it's also you can make it with the taper angle.
And so you put putting the no degree here.
So much to do with this one.
Openly gay in the design future.
So.
And unless one is to sort of the desired future, there is a several top of the slots is to rectangular
them and you spotted that slot on the 28th.
So let's see, step by step, selective select rectangle slot.
That's OK.
Select the face and the solid face and select the this face and you will see the release of the rectangle
sock length reads.
Let's make it a bit bigger then and let's make the legs also bigger.
And this is the depth.
Let's also increase the depth in five.
And so can you see a rectangle slot is created.
You can define the dimensions.
Will the slot.
So let's make it 50, that's OK and OK, so Sloat is created here and you see with the length of 30
millimeter and the which is the same, it was the ten and the depth is five millimeter.
The same can change the parameters of the.
The slowed.
Also changed the position, the date, the position, and you can change the positions, for example,
at the dimentia, you can change from the.
From this from these positions, also four of them.
Twenty five.
You can make that as your the project.
So.
She is the to obtain the rectangle slot, let's see as the purple the slots, for example, the.
Open this.
Salad bowl, bowl, slow to lick the face, the this face, and there is the dimensions for the slot,
for example, diameter, the depth and length.
So that's remain like this in case you see the.
You can also define the positions.
Let's make it 50.
And 25.
This week.
You see, the bowl slot is created with the reddish.
The radish and radish in the bottom.
The same added parameters, for example, the future diamond disposable diameter is 10, let's make
it smaller to see the difference.
OK.
OK, you see, that is the diameter is change.
At least let it feature.
Pekka.
So.
It this one.
Design feature slowed, you slowed.
So face.
This face, and that is the kind of thing the weeds steps, Colorado and the length, so the way it
is then the depth is five at smoke.
Let's try this one.
It is the located here and you can make it location.
It is the youth vote list.
Uh.
Make the view just to see the cross section, for example, that this one.
You see, it is that you thought that's why I called you --.
It's the you shape it, but that's why I called you salute.
The latest one.
To design future.
Sloat Kiesler, let's see the face where you want to make the sword and Sloat in selectees face also
near the top reached the top deps, the bottom bottom deps.
You should be bigger than the bottom, the top of it.
So it's 12 and 10.
This should be bigger than this in order to obtain the proper that slot.
Pocket press, OK?
It is the 10 list for this game you see here is octane.
It lets the see the.
The result on the cross section.
Used to sit in the tea shaped, so these diameter should be bigger than that is the matter.
So.
This is the Hunta, looks like the tea Sloat.
Pocket, OK, that's all about design features.
Now, just I would like to also speak about the here we have the Unite function in the substract and
intersect in order to do the disease.
Let's do one more element.
Let's make you can use the design feature.
OK, the sphere, the from the center will select the center point where you can make the position here
and define the for example, the meter.
That's the preview.
OK, that's enough.
That's OK.
I would like to make the unite and subtract means that it will unite the two objects.
Subtract it means that subtract one element from the another that intersect with the preview for us
intersection of the two elements.
So let's make the unite so in the Unite.
You can make here the Taj element and the two elements.
So if you, for example, selecta as a target element rectangle and selected to eliminate this sphere,
it means that the sphere will be added to the, uh, to the rectangle listecki.
So they will become one unit element.
So if, for example, let's move to unite you fight, for example, selected as a target and target
element as a sphere and to eliminate the direct angle.
And in this case, it will be viceversa the block.
That rectangle will be added to the sphere.
So.
Let's see the subtract, subtract, it means that, for example, if I like to select the target element
of this element and the total element that is, is this element, the the target element will remain
and the two elements just will be subtracted.
It is the position from the from the target element in this case.
In this case, the from the local angle five, for example, in the last week or so, you see target
element is remain it and two element is subtracted and the remaining six is the person on the on the
rectangle in the target element.
For example, in the subtitle, If I select the target elements here, in this case this fit and the
two elements of this one, you see the target element seriously meaning it.
And the two element is subtracted from the face.
From the face of the earth feared the case of the target element.
Last one is the Intersect, that's the intersection point of the two at the summit, as there's a target
element next to them and to the end of this one, you see subtraction point is all of these disappear,
just the remains, the subterfuge, the intersection point of the two elements.
This is the, uh, about united septet and intersecting points.
OK, so that's all for today.
Thank you very much.
See you on the next Lassus.