Well, welcome back on the tutorial from the Cut.
So today we will make the practice lesson and basically draw the all the components of the robot manipulator
starting from the base to until to the grippers.
So in the next lesson on the assembly techniques, we will make the assembly.
Will this.
Assembled this.
So today we just add all the components in this list.
So let's from the first element, it's the base.
So open the Phoenix file new.
And look.
So like Selecta.
That plane and place.
OK, so.
So firstly, draw the circle is the diameter is a 70 millimeter.
So.
Who?
There are some 70 and extruded on the heat of the three mm.
What I think.
Draw one more two circles under about the surface of this cylinder.
So on this very specific and the diameter was first one is 55 and the second is.
Fifty one, there's work on extruded.
On a distance of twenty eight point seven.
OK.
I'm united with the base, OK?
Select Shige selected this face for HASSOCK.
Broke the circle here in the city called.
Fires the OK and using the geometric constraint, make the point on the call of this point from the
cause of this.
And to that, this distance.
I saw something in the good.
OK, so extruded.
The election.
On the Bulan Selecta, subtract, OK?
So open the.
That future.
So, like the whole, uh, pattern in the layout, like the circle specified, the vector, this vector
point is the center of the circle, zero zero points so close and number is the.
Number eight on the.
Annualise three, divided by eight, so this is the horse race, OK?
The holes are created, so let's change the color of the element, menu it.
Object display selecta object came in from the Carlesimo can can make it yellow, but it's OK.
So we came hard, this sketch.
So first, everyone is ready.
Save it on the fire because we going to use it in the assembly.
First element, for example, you can open the fire, listen for a new fire and the robot arm press.
Okay, open the new file.
OK.
They can eliminate this one.
OK, let's start to the is radiuses to point twenty seven point five and.
So to them, it is 51.
Gitche.
Twenty seven point five.
Multiplied by two, the diameter extruded under the weight of two millimeter No.
Yes, to me and Mr..
And draw one more circle on the bottom side.
The evidence is safety for.
To.
Mystic's.
Twenty seven point five month to month contract.
This.
Once, judge.
Extruded from a distance of three.
OK.
Get the led to this face, OK?
Throw the rectangle here.
And I made a few little stratis.
Tim.
Will Cain.
It will define the.
The distance is thirty eight.
You can make like this distance from here to the center.
It's the first to deal with this one.
This distance from.
The.
And this distance.
So going to try to do the.
Suu.
And that is the tangent concerned, legitimately misconstrued.
Still, it is skewed and grow one more time squidge.
Can you make it feel at.
18.
OK, and define the distance from here to the center is to maintain distance from here to the center
is also maintain.
So and they selected this horizontal and intriguing.
Driving brought to the here to become the tainted, so.
The same on this site.
Until the.
We come to terms and so much.
So now is the security here, I select, select, selected this stage, and you U.S. can exclude it
now the distance of the extruders, 50 mm.
Yeah, right.
The 50 millimeter and unite Sarkin.
And here The Selecter transfer.
From here in Select, a single course selected this one and this one, this is six Rezac.
So last step is to make that this.
The Circle sketch selected this face to soak and select the circle.
OK, so let's draw the circle.
The damage to seven.
Make the distance between the sexes and this is zero.
And the distance from here to here.
It turned out this weekend.
Extruded in the distance of similar distances for.
Unite into this object, Rusnak.
Not least make the middle of this future so near future, but this future alone, the plan of these
seats.
OK.
So element is really less to make the hard this sketch.
Let the change the color menu, insert date object display select objects like color yellow.
OK.
OK, so.
Second element is really.
They sold.
File save it on the same.
While a complaint.
OK, so second element is really.
This next element is this this one of our robot manipulators.
So let's start the road, this element.
OK, Squidge, so like the plane in place, OK?
So draw the circle.
That's the.
Diameter is the.
Last I checked, the diameter, the bigger the today is to sixty three, six to three point five.
And the same.
Here and the distance is between them.
Eighty eight point five millimeters.
So we can make the.
Symmetric.
Orders to make the SM were put in the.
Matthew.
Go the rectangle in the.
And this distance is.
Seven.
OK, using the quick trim, just clean these elements.
On extruded.
In the distance of 2.5.
Let's look at the bases in the middle, that is a mistake list.
Check this one.
Should be extended.
And this should be dramaturgical, Ross is correct.
This one.
The correct so.
Finish units correctors.
So, ladies, this is OK.
Bro.
One more vehicle here still.
And then throw in the so-called.
The diameter is eighty one point five.
And.
Make offset of the school.
And this school.
Let's first
discuss the rest of their agenda distances to eliminate and OK.
So make it quick three.
To school, this small.
And to.
I want you to go to school, OK?
And let this also disable.
It is from.
And this is one end of the line here.
In the open.
We've set the course and that whole set of discourse on that direction.
OK, Project Growth, this one this week three.
This and this and this.
This.
Like his friend.
Just on this in this war.
Well.
This.
And this.
This for.
The same here, draw the line here.
Again, that road.
Your through.
You spend.
Anderson, that's the extruded.
So the two point five and United is the base and personal.
So this is created now is to make the.
These elements and the whole sort of the to circle here in this.
So first.
So.
It's the eleven point five.
Under the.
The same.
Four, five.
And they seem to be going for the same point, extrude them.
On the distance of three, unite, it is OK, so this is created now just to hold this remaining so
sketch so that this is OK, the whole diameter is a two millimeter.
It's in the middle.
So.
Selecta Circo know the two of hole here.
Constraint point on the course, and this is.
Yeah.
So.
On the court.
Småland.
To.
Extruded.
The this action, not united, subtracts from that object this week.
So the element is really let's define the color.
So date.
Object misplacement object to King.
Carla.
The yellow.
OK, so that's the height of this allowance, the sketch.
So this is the third element of the manipulatable.
It.
And open the new.
And Xfire.
Less work and less to continue the next 11 days, one we will obtain despite the legal option.
So let's open the new sketch.
Let this rain check.
Here.
Lines to distances.
Mm.
And just draw the this frame, then it will revolve around this excuse not to do this alone.
And so I meant to ask you.
Mr. Acharya, this is a twenty two point eight to eight.
Make them the tanjim, this and this.
There are over the age and so on the.
Make to offset.
And the distance of.
Two millimeters.
OK.
Close the cone to this one.
Should be vertical.
And trendy spot.
Klaus.
This and this and throw one more reference line here in the axis of rotation, convert it to the reference
and make the distance between this the first axis and the this is.
Eight millimeters, as you can often hear, the remold.
It's selected, that is, and this is what the vector is defined from here, the Xs and select, this
is all revolve around this axis.
But it's week.
I d so like the caller.
So much to object to.
Seafood.
Listen for a moment.
Open the New Holland.
This week, next element is this one.
OK, let's do this.
OK, first of the external here.
Using the biocentric, though.
Today.
20.
And that is the new.
We looked at this one.
He met.
And extruded from the distance or say, mm.
OK.
No selecta Skitch.
To discuss this week.
Grow again, rectangle here in the sun for the sun to.
And define the dimensions
18.
Eating.
Make them symmetric, this and this symmetrical around this axis, doing this and this, but on this.
Decent is the answer to this makes you so extruded.
And the depth is one point for me to subtract.
It's to.
Squidge.
So this side of the fence would draw the circle, the circle of the 16.
In the center.
16.
OK, extruded.
From a distance of.
Sighs Mm
mm, not surprising, but you light this.
Okay, so this Alimentarius.
Rudy.
OK, we can save it should the change of the caller.
Some like to object to common in this case to be made into black.
OK, OK, so let's to the hard decisions.
And this saw.
David.
I think.
Location is than the next element of the manipulator to open the file.
But it's OK.
Select the sketch and you can select this plain press council, so to draw the profile.
Like this and define the dimensions.
Distances.
Term.
This distance is
six miles to the Rhode
Island with a smaller scale.
OK.
OK, and then.
This distance is two.
This also from.
Six millimeter.
And this is also the 10 millimeter.
This is not the.
This is the milimeter.
This site.
So let's dig through this.
You can make the export of the synthetic value and the distances to the team, let's make it nine.
The OK.
So.
There is the feelings of the three millimeters here.
That make you feel it, so it's brillant.
These.
This.
So Mr..
This and this.
Next, it make
and.
So you think.
So let's to make the holes real for the little to zero point seven Lipnic.
Which promoted here.
Zero point seven.
OK, sketch this plane, OK?
But on the whole, here.
And the.
Distance from here to here is.
Mr..
And it's on the.
Geometrical strand of the center point, this is the center point of this.
Extruded.
The last election, then subtract.
The same.
This face to.
Two holes here.
And to.
Actually.
Close out.
This.
Going to check it out.
There's also.
Schoolkid.
This is not six or six is from the.
Here.
Six.
Our squad worked hard them.
To the future, Khalil.
They did.
Like Karen.
Kim.
So this is the.
And the next element, so let's call it six this weekend.
Open the new file.
OK, and next to this, so let's roll this element, select sketch selector playing this week.
Well, like Daniel, you can put the dimensions of the rectangle.
So do.
So the so called the.
So first here.
One point eight.
On.
The six here.
And Curtis.
Four point seven.
Four point seven million.
So let's throw the phrase small holes is the diameter subsidy.
Mm.
Three millimeter and the distance from the base.
From here to here is.
Four mm.
Let me take you to Mr..
And the distance between them is.
Minamata.
OK, let's this one.
To define the distance between them different and this is.
Well, and the distance between them is.
Nine millimeter.
The same ground holds near.
Make the mirrored.
And define the distance between the two homes.
Wolf.
Again, draw the hole here.
The same Democrats, three distance from the top edge is.
Ten point four.
Again, the meaning of the whole.
Around the Y-axis and the define the distance between the two falls is.
20 millimeter.
And again, the drove the whole under this all of the at eight, with the same axis of this hole
and its distance from the surge is 14.
From the center.
14.
Can you can finish it?
So the sketch is ready, extruded from a distance of two millimeters, so let this sketch.
And two millimetres this week.
Well, this is awesome, finish it defined.
Color or display so that this object, OK, define the color black.
To.
I.
So it.
OK, Max, element of the it's gripper, so open the leaks.
New file.
Professor Kay.
Selecta sketch, Darton plane and OK.
So that's the first lead role of this part of the element and.
Draw the line here.
And it's Lanxess.
92 millimeter.
OK, we can make it take this point, this point around this nexus.
Symmetric, connected to the difference line.
Make it all sit.
Symmetrical offset in the distance is.
To them now.
Not the 10, but we will make it five because.
Five a.m., OK, so.
Select the OK.
Made clear on this site that it is this five.
The same on this site.
They drove the two holes in the diameter of the three millimeter.
Not only to the role of this part of the elements who.
Go the line.
Starting from the sea.
Slurries is 28.
Nikita Offset.
Not a symmetric.
And also distance.
Not just in general, the.
Learn here and make it the parallel.
Not equally, the parallel this and this is parallel to define the distance as a.
Five millimeter.
You can make two easier.
So in this government.
Also, the train, this part.
That's a different angle here.
From the House through this one and the design of this distance
14.
In this small and defined angle is one hundred forty five.
We're going to.
And the here this element.
Do metal, cross trains, open metal, German straight.
Mark.
Yeah.
And you to St..
Point on the growth.
Screw's.
So how can you with this line or convert to the reference and make the that?
So, of course, this this.
Oh, this won't work.
Well, you have to put in the numbers.
Future.
This from this new.
Around this time.
The.
Misconstrued.
Coincidence of.
This.
And this.
This and this.
Close it and finish.
So the.
Profar was created, excluded.
That is of.
Three millimeter.
So like this one.
And Rick.
Let's defined a little.
Put.
Select the book.
OK.
The same black.
So are these parts.
The group that is created now, the last is the
board for holding the defection to elements of the mine operator.
It's easy to pull a new hire.
So firstly, just to save the Greber.
Can it can you Hyam?
Kenny.
Sketch displayed.
The circle is the diameter is just three.
And extruded from a distance of.
Five millimeter.
You find the caller.
So this is.
That's the most simple.
Shavitt.
No case so serious, that's all for today.
It's the all the components for dramatically Rupert later in the Assembly election, as I mentioned
before, we will make the also learned assembly techniques and make assemble the.
These are all the elements, this whole element, nine elements in order to make that this manipulated.
Thank you very much.