Let's start our lesson.
Today, we learn about extrude and recall features to create the basic and simple part, we will start
with the extra features Lechter.
Create a new file model and then OK.
The extrudes is a process of taking two dimensional profile and converting it to the tree by giving
it to some sequence as a simple example of this would be taking the circle and convert it to the cylinder.
Once you had to create the profile, a profile you want to extrude, activate, extrude, Coman.
So let's firstly draw.
Simple, two dimensional sketch, select the plane.
OK.
So.
Let's throw the first rectangle.
And put the dimensions.
For example, here is one hundred fifty millimeters and the.
It is.
Eight mm.
So then, for example, we can add the circle circle by the center of all the people in a circle and
put the animation for the circle, for example, you can make it sound.
Mm.
And if you extrude this.
It will not be excluded because you see here intersection between circle and the rectangle, so it will
it will be not extruded in order to extrude your skin should be unique and close it.
So we will use the quick trim function in order to cut off unnecessary sketch.
So this one.
This one and this one.
So now it is open system and this is totally closed system and we can make extrude.
So in order to make the extra do you see here in rebar, extrude function and press this in this here
in the selected course, you have to select the cover.
It's automatically selected.
You see the here they selected and in here you can make the define the thickness of this scale.
So in this case, it's twenty five millimeters.
You see an upward variation of twenty five millimeters.
So you should press here, OK, you will get a solid function extruded.
Extruded
your sketch.
So in the similar way, in a similar way, for example, if we make the return to the return to the
sketch, we can make symmetrical options on the dialog bar.
So you press the extrude if you open here, there is in the start point, it is the symmetric value,
if you like the symmetry, if you see from the sketch, it will be made symmetric.
Twenty five inch upward and downward extruded and totally 50 millimeters.
So if you look you get.
Extruded sketch with the 50 millimeters in which so.
Next, this is reward future's reward is the process of taking two dimensional profile and reward it
about the centerline to create the three dimensional geometric shapes that are actually symmetric while
creating a sketch for the whole future.
It's important to think about the causational shape that will define the 3D geometry once it is revealed
about an axis.
So let's open new.
OK, let's firstly delete.
This would like and exclude, delete and delete this image, so C.H..
OK, plain press, OK, to make the reveal, let's firstly draw one simple sketch, so.
Let's the selected profile.
And the rope line is, let's make it one hundred.
And draw one line, it is let's make it 30 millimeters.
Fifty millimeters.
And this one, is it sort of three?
And what it is, 50 millimeters.
And here you can make.
The same.
Legs, and this one is also let's make it 40 millimeters.
And this is in the same length.
And this is all the same length, and this is let's make the three.
And it is let's make it 50 and in where to go, so 90 degrees, so.
This one and this one.
OK, we draw the sketch now.
Let's throw one line here.
It's a center line.
So in order to make a rotation around this and convert it to the reference and distance.
Yes, let's make its distance between this and this.
Twenty five.
And here, if you open the export, there is the Revo function, OK, Prester a wolf and for the select
group and select this quote is selected automatically by the index.
So in the specify for the vector.
So let's for the specified for the exit or vector select this axis.
So it's axis of rotation.
And you see here the sketch is revolved around this axis.
So you see you can make that angle of the rotation.
It's in this case it's six handle is three hundred sixty degree.
So for example, if you add one hundred eighty percent or so, you see it's all in one hundred eighty
degrees.
All you can make.
One hundred, two hundred seventy.
So you see here this.
Is revolved around this axis, so it is the remove function.
So in the.
In the extruder extrude function, there is several additional options for the extrude coalman to be
added in the three dimensional geometry.
Now you see this function, so you see this reward.
So let's do it.
This one.
Until this one, let's select the New Age, for example, select and explain and press, OK, let's
draw one for one rectangle using three from the center.
OK.
And put the dimensions using the European dimension, for example, the length is two hundred and eight.
One hundred fifty.
So then extrude it in.
50 millimeters, so you select distance 50 millimeter.
So it's extra okay now.
OK, select the sketch again.
Select this face, you see, it is the red becomes red like this face, and it will be normal to displace
this face.
So from here.
So like the arc.
Using.
Two or three points.
So.
OK, so put the emission for this example, the diameter is.
It's 90 degrees also, you can make the same mistake, for example, if you remember, there is more
symmetric function, you can make symmetric this one in this one around this exit will become symmetry.
So now I would like to extrude this out, but in order to do this are extruded.
So still we have to close it count.
So I have to close this point using the simple line.
So you see it is closed and now I can extrude.
If I will not close this line, it will be not so extrude.
So you see.
It is extruded.
It is the one we will draw more complex shapes, so another way.
For example, let's make clothes, this suit and the clothes of this one.
OK, I will show one more thing one more time.
Extrude, extrude of this.
And here you see in the balloon, in the balloon there is the Unite Unite function.
That means if you press this unite and in the selected body you select the rectangle that's the extruded
before it will be unite.
It will unite two elements.
It will they will become one element.
So always when you make such kind of sketch, you have to make unite of two elements.
OK, so this one and this one become one element.
So select in this one.
Get from here to like this one and delete.
So let's I mean, these are let's now see how to make cut substraction.
So select the extrude and the for the for the select could select this olg.
And the from the balloon you see here does attract so in the direction is in the upward direction from
the here in the extrude function, open the direction and he'll make the rest that.
So it will be downward.
And if you press that, OK, this.
ARC will be subtracted from that this rectangle, it is the one way of making substraction.
Option, so let's the delete this one and then, I mean the initial rectangle or pressed again exclude
so select the are you make a reverse direction and if you open the boolean, there is.
Function of intersection, if you make the intersection and press.
OK, this rectangle will be disappeared.
All the remaining part will be intersection between the arc and the rectangle.
So ARC will be animated.
So, you see, it is the.
It is the intersection we have seen unite or subtract in intersection, so we see the intersection.
This is the method of moving in the extrudes extrude function.
This is the methods of the BO1 extrude function.
Next up.
Of the functions, that's the call it limits on the extra there are there is a limit S. So here limit
section, it's the starting and end point.
So in the limitation has the various options to define the start and end limits of the future.
If you open the highest start point, there is the we have seen the symmetric where we will live and
we will see the other options in the limit.
So from the start, from all of us in the end of.
So let's start in the.
Uh, first one is the let's go until the next.
So in order to see how to use it until the next, let's firstly go one next and let's do it this one
and do it this one and let's end this rectangle.
So.
And.
In here, you see the Darton.
Is additional that on plane will have to put additional planes on the existing ships on the next lesson.
Now, let's select that plane from here at a distance and say that this plane, this face you see from
this face the distance, for example, let's make it the.
Let's make it bigger.
For example, the 80 and hear the numbers, let's drill two to that one place and so to that one place.
Starting from there, this plane is created.
Distance is 80.
Mm mm.
From the here to the two planes is created and the sketch.
And select the dishearten plan and press looking.
So.
Let's drove the one rectangle here.
OK, two points.
And the.
Selective finish.
So Rectangle is.
Is created in the plane and the make extruded.
This is and it's 50 millimeter press.
OK, that is the mistake because it's an intersection and that make Eagle known and it's great.
So.
And the selected this.
This plane, rock and roll.
Smaller, rectangular.
Excluded.
So if you select here and wear blue until the next, you see it automatically and well goes until the
next.
Next extruders future, if you select the starting point also until the next, it will continue.
The starting point will be until then, until the this in the first extruded extruded future.
This is until the next.
If you make the value in Sipi, this is hard to use until the next.
Limited function, limited function in the extrude.
So next one is the until the selected.
So it will remain low and then this will select.
The next one is.
Okay.
Let the delete.
Jerry.
Delete this one.
Let's try this one, gay extrude.
So like this one until the selected here.
Their value is until the selected and the direction is in this case, let's reverse the direction until
the.
So in this case, you have to select the phase where you want to extrude this.
So let's select this phase.
It is the you see, it becomes red, you should say, like this one.
This will become let's make it zero.
So it will become the extruded until the this face press.
Okay.
This is the only way of making extruded function.
So.
Next is let's do this one, next is let's select extrude this one this year through an issue selected
through all.
And from here, they'll subtract and this one that will go through all this.
Let's make zero.
You see it going through all substract around this big rectangle, so it is subtracted.
So.
That's all of today's lesson on the next lesson.
We will see how to put that in place on existing.