Hello, Soudas, let's start our lesson today to learn about the Putina that took place, additional
that took place on the existing three dimensional scale.
This is a very important topic because when you do a complex shapes, you lead to additional that took
place in order to combine the complex projects.
So we will see different types of the dart in place, how to put on the existing three dimensional space.
There are there are many different types you can make that put the data in place at a distance or at
the angle or B sector and several options.
Let's start and see step by step, all of them in order to continue to date and plan.
We have to firstly.
Sketch, simple project.
So select a sketch select plane.
For example, we can draw a rectangle in the center and they can put the dimensions 200, for example,
press enter and this is, for example, one hundred twenty press.
And then, for example, we can make the chancellor on this edge, select the channel for function.
And then between this and this make.
For example.
60 mm presenter from Channel four is created, the element is.
Created.
And make extruded.
Let's make it one hundred fifty and press Prestwick now.
On this project, we will draw the Dataplan
here selecter that to play in the dirt plane function is activated and if you open here, there is several
options of the plane.
You will see all of them step by step.
Firstly, you start from the Dutton plane at a distance.
So the distance that the plane and here select plane and object, you have to select the phase where
you want to draw that plane in the distance, for example, displays like this one.
So you see the direction of the Delta plane knew that when plane is created and the distance between
this face and this starting plane, an eight millimeter.
So you can change it as you want, for example, with 100 millimetres.
And so you can also change the direction.
And you can also.
Change the number of the data, for example, to all.
Three and so on, the more that took place, the kind of more that place is needed when the making the
surface projects.
So we will see this in lessons when we start to make sort of this policy.
So in now we need only one is enough.
So, Rezac.
So you see the Darton plane at a distance from this face is created, then you can draw any sketch on
this cartoon plane, for example, the sketch press that they created that plane.
OK, it will be normal and can do, for example, sort of the any amateur if you see the circle is created.
Exactly.
On created that plane.
Now you can make extrude on sole function within this circle.
This is the first method.
That's the first method that the distance.
We'll start to play, you can make that doesn't play at a distance, for example, on this phase or
on this phase.
And so.
Next method of the Guttenplan is at the angle, so in order to do the templating, let's do with this
one stage, they start to plan.
So let's remain this project.
So selected that plane.
From the type select the angle at Select the planner object is the same as the face and the select Oliner
Object, select this, for example, Edge.
You see that template is created at the angle of these.
It's it's the 100.
It is the 120 degrees you can change it in any, for example, 40.
Or you can take it is, for example, 70 and so on, it is the Daptone plane at the end of
next step that the plane is to be sector by sector is a method creates the plane, which lies at the
midway between the two selected phases.
So let's firstly delete this one and this extrude and then the sketches will and create New Schaik,
for example, using the profile sketch.
Such kind of simple element.
And extruded.
Let's remain one hundred fifty, okay, next is selected up on the plane, and here you see the option
of the beef sector selected B sector.
As I mentioned, this creates the Darton plane midway between the two selected faces for the first option
of the phase.
Let's select this phase for the second.
Let's select this one.
Now, you see that one plane is created midway between these two.
That selected face is presently.
Tom.
Next is the date to create the Dayton plane, the with the three points, so firstly, delete this one
and send it to that one plane.
Here you select data, two calls on point and you can select three points.
First point, this one.
So you can put this one in the third point.
Let's look at this one so that plane is created.
So not complaining.
Three point is created.
Mix of type of the plainness attention contemplate in order to see the how to use the 2013 plane less
so one.
Slender.
OK.
Let's close the circle and excluded, for example, a good number, 400 and from the that selected Guttenplan.
And the press, the type that is the tangent and select the object, you should select the so that complain
that the tangent to the death cylinder is created less.
Delete the dot and blink, delete the cylinder, delete this or go one step of the dot and blame is
the only cause.
This is a very important talking plane and very often used to that plane.
So select the sketch.
But that's OK.
Used using the spline studio to throw any spline landfill's.
Press, OK, and select that, Blaine.
And the date and place and the select the point and the direction and select that this point and you
see.
The darkened plane.
He's created this is the method of the creating the date and place, and there are very important,
as I mention it, because when you when you start to drop the complex object, you will need all this.
You have to use the several methods of the darkroom as SARS, that's the Anex systems, is required
to throw the anything simple case on the button, please.
So let's firstly delete this was and continue our lesson, and now I would like to show you some options
of the universe.
This is the view modification options in order to continue is a view modification.
I would like to draw a simple project.
For example, the diameter is one hundred.
And let's throw one centerline here
and convert.
It to reference.
And no one line here, for example, the.
15.
And the angle is nine degrees.
And make me roll it out along the line.
And AndroGel one, Arkia.
And also draw one circle, for example, the diameter is eight.
And as you remember, there is the title Shin, but then the cool selected discourse in this circle
and the method is the loudest circle.
This five point is the center of the circle and the count is three and angles, one hundred two in the
press with King and.
Three of these unnecessary parts, but this finish.
It is created, extruded, so like this one or it's too big for us, too enticing is enough.
Yes.
Let's make 20 Rezac.
Prestage.
It is something wrong?
Let's deal with this one, the sketch, this face, OK?
Still, firstly, two circles.
This 60.
And for example, 30.
Extruded.
For example, the 50 in the unite with this one, Rezac.
It's created now let's see humidification common issue here.
Open, there are several options of the new modification, first one is associated with the edge, this
original form shaded with the S, next one is associated.
The shaded, this represents a multitude of shades without visible, if I press, the edge will become
visible.
You see?
Without visible edge, next one is like Frame with DeMetz, this represents a model in the way frame
the heat and it's a great out you see in the right frame and the.
They hit an eighth grade out next one by frame without.
Year by frame with a hidden edge, why frame this hidden image, you see, why frame the hidden edge?
The edge is not visible.
Next is static y frame.
This represents the model in a Y frame along the way, along with the hidden edge.
Along with the heathen age, let's the.
Put the original with the edge eggs, next is the Orient you here, you see Orient view in the Orient
view, you can look the old project in a different way.
The for example, in the three matricular or.
Torquil, you see?
Or is it regrew?
Or until.
What do you and so.
This is the use of the your project, this.
That's all for today, Lessem.
The Today lesson is we learn about the Duplin planes and the views of the Owl project, that Delta plays
a very important topic.
As I mentioned, and the Today lesson is over and next lessons, we will see the practices on the extrude
and recall function as well.
Additionally, the took place season on the next lesson.
Bye bye.