Hello, Soudas, let's start our next lesson today to make practice on sexual function.
So let's open the new find.
Dope and let's make it an exercise.
Six and smaller Dresnok.
Today, do make sure that this exercise is using the extrude firstly will throw the base of the this
project and this particular end up.
So let's start a little press sketch.
And select a plane, for example, X and Y, plane and press.
OK, so let's start to draw base in order to draw the base line.
Let's make the rectangle, for example, from the center in a rectangle and put the dimensions.
He says sixty to sixty using the rapid dimension.
60.
And 60 plus articles, let make the Chaillot here on the corners with a radius of 10 millimeters.
So using the field here, so like this one in this one and until the time and also through other four
corners.
So press escape and grow the.
Holes with the diameter is 10 millimeters select a circle.
And the hole in the center of the arc, 10 millimeter, the same, you put you in here press escape,
if you see here also the very small hole with the diameter of five millimeter in the same axis of the
the bigger holes and the midpoint of this line.
So let's throw the hole at the same axis, for example, here in the middle five.
And they're using the geometrical screen here.
It was the midpoint.
So we have to make midpoint of this circle and select this one end of this line so it will become in
the midpoint.
So we have finished with the base so we can exclude it in the distance of 15 because it's 45.
And so the difference is the 15.
Mm, so Precedex trued.
The discharges of dramatically selected and here the distance is close to 15 Presta.
Okay, so the bases created now is to grow the.
Cylinders in the top of the this base, so let's throw this or go to scooch selected this phase, Listecki
draw the circle here in the middle.
So the circle is.
The diameter is.
So millimeter.
Then extruded until.
And and do so limit to suppress, extrude and make it did they release 30 millimeter press AK?
So.
So, like the sketch selected this face, basically.
The circle with the diameter of 20 millimeter selectors extrude and change the direction in here, that
and we can make until the selected and until the selected, you have to select this face and hear the
substract.
This week.
Last step is to do.
This element.
Look.
Selectors Cage selected this field as a key.
Draw the line here.
That line.
Let's check the word colonial here, using the geometrical constraint, make the bed and
make mirrors along this line and distance was 10 millimeters between these lines.
Through the same on this part.
Make it vertical.
And make it Meerut.
And define the distance between the lines and MM.
And here using that project could make a captive of this.
Two lines this week, then using the quick trim.
OK, make the cut of this parts.
OK.
Then using the exploded.
We hope there is mistake's.
We will check.
OK.
There is the mistakes do make it correct.
Firstly, it is one.
You see here, there is no so using the extreme.
Make it coincident, you see, here is the this one.
This is cool.
Look, I see it now looks to me this one, this, all this and this one.
This was extrudes.
This one also.
And still, it's mistake.
It's through the.
What is this school going to say active with this line, Kate?
Strutt.
The Senate now works, yes, change the direction the last election and the distance is 15.
And here to subtract this, OK?
No.
It works, we have finished with this first exercise, let's make it safe.
And let's continue with the second one.
You did this one, so let's open the new file.
Model get exercise at seven.
Translocate.
Skitch.
Selective blame.
OK, so.
Firstly, the base is 90 plus 30 millimeters and the total length is 120 millimeters and he is 60 millimeter.
So firstly through the rectangle.
So make it a donation is one hundred twenty.
In 60 mm.
So there is the radius of here, a radius of 30 millimeters, so make the field the radius of 30 millimeters
here.
And let's make it.
Trim, trim, so.
This is St..
General Surkov and Deselecting, let's start with the circle, so.
And the damage to this hurricane is 10 millimeters.
And the distance.
At this point.
Yes, 30 mm.
And the direct anger here.
This is this.
Distance is 30 millimeter.
And this distance also.
So the MM.
So, Andrew.
Two lines here.
Additional lines.
And the make then reference line.
In the using geometric constraint, make them.
Six.
And also using go straight.
Make the point.
Linda could.
So.
In at this rectangle and these two circles now each step to make extrude of 15 millimeters here.
So it's 15 Infl Ocky.
The sketch.
Selected the face.
OK, here now is step to obtain this part.
Throughline here in.
Make it vertical.
And select selected distance here.
Mm.
And the big project was.
With this line.
And make quick trim this.
And this extrudes.
The last election on distance of 10 millimeter, this like 10.
You subtract week.
Ken, D-line.
OK, so press the sketch, so let's face this, OK?
The road director here.
And put the nation's.
It's the 40.
And they make to distance.
This, this.
This distance is 60 and this is the 14th and the time to make and move to make this trip.
Suki.
And extruded.
Here he the Unite.
And the distance of this is a in the distance of 20 kilometres.
Cage, these, OK, and drew one more rectangle.
He did a distance of.
OK, so this line.
The distance is five.
This is five.
So extruded.
Reverse direction distances.
And mm, and there is no united, but in this case that this key.
Last step is to make whole.
Sketch this surface, there are some key.
We can draw the circle here is the diameter is 20 millimeter.
Using the geometrical strain.
Here.
The midpoint is one point.
This one is the midpoint of this line and this one is midpoint of this line.
So it is in the center subtract.
The last election with Kate End, where is still selected until the face.
Press Wookey.
That this second project is all to finish it.
OK.
We are successful today is this one okay, open the new file on the Knicks new fire.
Sighs.
It Dresnok.
And so, like this huge select the plane Brazuca.
So.
Let's throw first and the circle.
With the diameter of.
It is, mm.
So draw referenced lines with the angle of.
For Defrays.
Convert them to their first line.
Draw the circle.
Wanted them to do that for the police.
20 millimeter.
And using your mental ghost named.
Point on the good point.
On this curve.
And this point on this, the close it.
Make.
Three.
Draw the circle here, also the diameter of the.
Could remove these parts and make it select the pattern, the course.
The layout is circular.
Select because this one No.
You're not connected to just a single cause, this one and this one.
The layout is so good.
Specified point in this one.
And the number is the full.
The pitch angle is thirty five to forty five.
It's the 90.
That's Vicki.
And trained.
These parts.
The.
Closet and extrude this cage in the distance of 10 millimeter.
Mr. A goes in order to make the cylinders so briskets.
This this was.
Did all the circles in the center here of this.
Mine and the diameter of this circle is 60 millimeter.
And extruded from the lens of 30 millimeter here in the bowl, make it unite with the base.
OK.
And selected this face.
Sketch, OK, draw the circle here.
To the circus.
So at the moment, first of all, is.
50.
And this one.
And this one is.
30 millimeter.
Glue's.
Extrudes.
The last election and the distance is the 15 and not unite, but in this case, subtract this.
And there is the sketch, this face, basically.
Draw the circle here in the middle and select the diameter is 20 millimeter.
Glue's extrudes.
The worst direction and and values until selected of this face subtract Rick.
Last step is to roam the halls, stage this space this week and do.
Two bulls here.
Okay, firstly, drew, the reference to.
This whole to the reference and the.
The meat of this whole is.
40 millimeter.
And draw one reference line here.
Let go and convert it to the rest of the school and grow your small pool with the diameter, it is four
millimeter and using geometric constraint.
My point on this point.
Here.
And make it Mr..
Around this central axis, this OK, now make extrudes.
Reverse direction of the release and values until selected and selected to this subtract this week.
This last project is over the finish, it will finish today.
Listen next.
See you on the next lesson.