Let's start our next practice lesson on the extra functions.
Today, we will see three or more exercises.
First one is this.
Let's start with this project.
Let's open the index.
Press the sketch.
So like the plane and the press.
OK, so let's firstly draw the circle on the central axis.
And the put the dimension is 50 millimeter.
And draw one more circle is it will be reference circle with the diameter of diameter is 70 millimeters.
So convert this.
Second thoughts go into reference.
Circle, so it is converted to the reference circle and draw one line here, vertical line.
It is also the reference line and drew two circles.
One.
Okay, and the diameter of this circle is.
20 millimeter.
Using the geometry constraint and the point on nuchal function, select the center and this vertical
line the same.
Center of the circle and this.
Circo.
And Drew.
Line here, this with.
And line.
The scene here.
And make the distance of these lines.
20 millimeter.
And make this line in this line, so tangent.
There is something wrong with this peaceful.
The distance between this line and this volume.
Kate.
It's 20, make it 20 this, then make it quick three.
This one, this one and this one's.
And draw the circle, this small circle here.
The diameter of 10 millimeter.
Then using that pattern function, make paternal, the school single curved this one, this, this,
and this is circular layout.
The center is this one.
We did this and it is one hundred twenty.
This would k and make three of these unnecessary parts us to close.
Now you can make the extruded using the extrude function.
Extrude is around the ten millimeter this week, so the base is created now is drawing the next elements
of the project.
So like the sketch.
Selected these fees, Brazuca.
Draw the circle in the middle.
With the diameter of 40 millimeter.
And extruded.
In the length of 30 mm, you're right.
Mm.
And using the boolean logic, that's the way you can make to unite the base, but it's OK.
Is next is Drew the on on this face.
OK.
Draw the circle with the diameter of 30 millimeter, this AK and using the extrude function, we will
make the subtract change the direction and they until selected of.
This is.
It's not unite in this case if you subtract so breastwork.
Last step is to make the hole here so it is in the degree or one hundred twenty degree, so in this
case, we will need an additional.
Reference to Blaine.
So in order to make the reference that Tom DeLay certainly makes Cage so like the.
This faith and press, okay, so draw the line here.
And draw a line here, make the angle between this and.
This line.
Let's start first day with this one and draw the line.
This.
And maybe the angle between this line.
And this line, one hundred twenty.
No.
Susan Davis is.
Make it in this D-line.
One hundred twenty and.
Conrad.
These lines to dereference.
This line.
And dismantle the Nationals and the.
Throw the dart and play here.
Selected that Tamburlaine and are to blame the select.
Point on the direction.
And select at this point, and that's OK.
So you made the one additional thought and blame here and draw a circle on this topic play.
Squidge.
Lugt.
This week.
So draw the circle.
To Dimitris.
Five millimeter.
Distance between the center of the circle on this point is.
Fifty millimeter.
That circle is created now is can make it.
Extrudes.
And I you can make.
And subtract.
OK.
The whole issue of Danity on the.
The required position.
So the same can make that complaint here.
Let's go live to the sketch and draw one more line here.
Define the distance between this.
This.
One hundred twenty converted to the reference.
And finish selected to blame.
This point in, OK.
Sketch selected, they start to play.
Skitch.
They start to clean, OK?
Mm, present and the distance between the descent.
On this point is.
Five millimeter.
Mm hmm, distance and the distance is from this point to this point is 15 mm.
Extrudes.
Rather than action.
Substract Milkie.
Should you hold this obtained?
This is the first exercise for today's lesson.
Now we will see the second one, this exercise.
OK, let's continue the Circle project.
Open new file.
Call it exercise.
Then this week, select a sketch, define the plane and press the second descent, this one less start
to draw the list project.
Ricky.
Define select the profile.
Draw the line here.
This kind of shape defined the.
Dimension's.
Latest.
Mm.
Certainly can make the distance east and heat is 40 millimeter.
And this distance is the key.
And I think this this is already really define it.
Make to feel it.
On this path, it is sterilizes three millimeter.
And the same here, Dan mm.
And the heroes and mm.
The society is ready, we can make extruded.
Is the 50 to.
This week.
You can make the ads blend.
Mm, this one and this one also.
This week.
Now, you can make the whole
passage so that this phase this week.
Draw the hole in the same.
OK.
They mm.
The distance between this line and this line is.
Then.
And this distance.
Is also 10 millimeter.
You can make the of this whole round of snow centerline so we can make an additional little line.
Yes, it's going to be a 10 millimeters.
And milimeter.
And so this is it should be sorted.
Mm, yes, it's correct in the lead and.
Draw one more additional line here, circle here with the diameter is six.
Using geometrical streambed.
Midpoint.
D-line circle on this one, so it is in the midpoint and the distance between this and this is ten to
twenty five millimeter.
Extruded.
The last election substract Ruki.
No selecta Skitch.
Celiac disease, milk.
Drew.
Rectangle.
The distance of the rectangle defined this is 60
and this is 30 millimeter.
This distance.
This 10 millimeter.
And this distance.
He's also 10 millimeter
can make the at.
Is the five millimeters of rain is important physically?
Twice in the last only source of life.
Extruded.
Extrudes.
Remember, the last election in the distance is 30 millimeter and the soundtrack this week.
Selecta Skitch.
So this face, Prestwick.
We drove the circle here.
The diameter is 20.
Using the geometry.
Constrained make it midpoint.
This circle of midpoint of this line and this circle, this midpoint of this line extruded.
Through that distances five millimeter, subtract Listecki, the same sketch displays Listecki.
All the soul go.
Is the damage to the storm this week extruded?
Extruded.
The last election rallies until selected of this these face.
Suki.
So we'll take it.
So they can project this on and let's continue the thought last of this project.
OK, let's continue with this project.
Opened the new film.
Linksys, 11 Rezac.
Select a select lane and
draw the rectangle, for example, by the center.
Define the dimensions using that up in dimension.
The length is one hundred twenty, and it is.
Fifty millimeter.
Draw the circle, the diameter is 20 millimeter.
Using the geometry constrained midpoint, May made this circle midpoint of this line and define the
distance between this line in the center of the circle is five millimeter.
Yeah.
Using the profile.
Draw the line here.
Convert to ARC through the arc and draw the line to define the length of the.
This is.
Chieftain.
And the.
The diameter.
These distances, 10 millimeter.
Can't make it Meerut.
Now, this centerline.
OK, define the distance between this and this.
Is 30 millimeter.
Make the quick trim this part.
So it is finish it, close it extruded on the distance of 10 millimeter.
OK.
So like the sketch, I like this phrase, that's OK.
Draw the circle here.
In the midpoint, if the distance is the diameter is for the millimeter.
40 millimeter and extruded.
And the distance of.
20 millimeter on the Bulan, make it inside the base.
OK.
The sketch, these fees bresnik.
Draw the circle one more with the diameter is 30 millimeter.
They select excellent function.
In this case, reverse direction, the distances, the 10 millimeter and the Bulan, is subduct sooky?
So let the sketch again with this face as we came through again, the circle with the damage to this
in this case, 10 millimeter.
Extruded on the reverse that in this case, we can use and wait until the selected until of left to
this face, you see and subtract.
Okay.
So thought last project is almost finished.
Well, here we can make this eggplant.
This face, this face in the distance is these five millimeter.
And.
Basically.
The project is finished and the lesson of the today also to finish its season on the next Lesser's.