Hello, friends.
Uh, look, we discuss about the interface of Anex.
Uh, so before the starting of its interface, we will discuss about, uh, the introduction of Anex.
So Anex is a.
OK, and software, it means computer aided drafting and computer aided machining and also we can,
uh, use for computer engineering, it means we can analyze, uh, we perform the analysis in that.
So basically it releases in nineteen seventy three, uh, which simplifies complex product designs.
Yeah.
We can uh, uh, simplify, uh, design various products and not really model.
Uh, it is a very simple, useful and powerful software.
It is a parametric software in that we can easily modify by, uh, changing and uh and it's uh to come
on to uh we will discuss about what is, uh, that come on to.
OK, uh, this is a part navigator.
Uh, yeah.
That's a model by that we can modify, uh, after the modeling we can, uh, delete uh, some entities
and some uh uh uh lines, sketches and uh uh, any command by the uh by getting on there.
Right.
Uh, Anite uh by clicking on that.
Uh, Right.
What we can and hope that like this, uh like just uh this is, uh, circularly uh if we click on that,
the secretary is and I suggest it allows you to perform a video editing action on those features.
Yeah.
That's, uh, uh, I, uh, that, uh, by that we can edit, uh, the feature by clicking on, uh,
there.
So annexes, uh, modeling so we can and does in the next software, uh, by double clicking on Anex,
I can we can open, uh, the next software and this is uh, uh, interface of software by clicking in
that logo, double clicking on that logo.
Uh uh, we can exert uh the software.
Uh uh, you can check by clicking on that.
Uh, I can you, uh, double click on that.
I can you just go exert uh.
So if you, uh there is a file by clicking there, you can uh, uh, go to, uh, new page, uh, or
you can perform a new modeling, uh, by open if you have already, uh, more than you want to open,
uh, that model.
You can easily open there just like there if you click on open, uh, the open, uh, the navigation,
you can navigate your model and that open automatically like that.
Uh, if you want to, uh, if you uh, by clicking on there, you can select other options, other format
files and other format file.
Uh, it automatically, uh, selected third party format.
Uh, only party files is visible on there.
Uh, if you click on all files, uh, you can navigate all type of files just like that.
You can check if you stress analysis and this is a step forward file, we can, uh, just just check
your system file.
It also will be open, um, if you want, then you can open it, uh, click and then go in and then
the file will be open.
Um, and then, uh, this is not, uh, restricted.
You can also exit by clicking on there and also is mentioned here.
Uh, so, uh, all that new open policy will be here, this is a menu in that we, uh, can, uh, got,
uh, more options, just like import uh uh, use this, uh, buy that.
We can change the views, just like when you click.
Is that the whole page of that will cover all years and that will be honored.
Uh, that will be right.
And this is, uh, uh, all of the, uh, that not for us.
Uh, look to this resort pools, uh, by clicking on their tools, you can also, uh, record the screen
by clicking on here.
It's a shortcut of five.
Uh, if we click on there, those key recording is automatically start, you know, need to, uh, install
any other screen recorder in there.
You can, uh, uh, uh, if you want only the recording in, uh, annex software, you can use that
often record, uh uh, more desired.
It is, uh, Kampot.
OK, uh, that will start a new page by clicking in there new.
There will be come on.
You file, uh, with.
This is a.
There are very options, you can see this is a compartment.
Actually, this is an inspection for analysis and simulation for analysis.
You can by clicking on there, you can see the next natural level of training and so many chances,
uh, we can use a little little use for our drafting.
And it's also useful for drafting useful motion study, for starting not really modeling.
You need to click on a model and then select model or this is assembly for the start, uh, for, uh,
creating assembly.
If you have already, uh, um, models that you can use assembly and they are two type of assembly,
Top-Down assembly and what kind of Bottom-Up Assembly and assembly you can create the parts in.
Uh, uh, if you have no parts you can uh, design a part in, uh, assembly, uh, interface.
If you have no uh, if you have already a part, uh, you can navigate it.
Um, that is for, uh, Bottom-Up Assembly.
Oh.
Let me start from Melbourne by clicking.
Yeah, you can never get file for saving by clicking there, you can change and but that's done by clicking
there you can make a name.
3-D modeling, 30 models.
I'm thinking the, uh, the all files will be saved in that, uh, folder by clicking.
Yeah, you just need to press controls and all the files will be saved.
That for you.
No need to, uh, navigate, uh, interpretively.
Let me click on Model.
By clicking and then click on OK?
Just wait a second.
Yeah, it's open.
If you install and it's first time, uh, a little bit will be slow, so don't take the danger of further
use, uh, uh, multiple, uh, multiple times effectively use it will be more powerful.
Move faster.
OK, then.
This is, uh, option five.
We already discussed about this and this is assembly in that there are more and many options, but that
we can add our part just, uh, that I already see about that by clicking on air, you can navigate,
uh, the new part, uh, already designed, but, uh, you can see already see.
But yeah.
But there you can navigate from there.
Yeah.
You can just uh see this, a 3D model that I created already.
Uh uh then by changing we can change the format of file from there.
Yeah.
We can also create a new part from there.
This is uh uh uh hold on.
Assembly making.
Okay.
We can select, uh, component.
OK.
You can start a trading morning from there or this is a schedule for making a sketch or creating, uh,
selecting, uh, clean up by selecting a plane, we can create a sketch.
Yes.
You need to click on sketch and then select a plane just like that.
You can select a.
Yeah.
You can select the plane if you want to, uh uh, by design,
by clicking, if you, uh, missing some come on from there, you can click on that space directly.
You can check, uh, multiple, uh, uh, options from there.
Just to be if you click, uh, dust like that, see, uh, if you uncheck ORENDER, then you can see
there's, uh, no option.
Uh, there exist.
And, uh, if you click on here and you got a render, the simple, uh, rendering, uh, just like
if you click tools just to use the tools, if you click are tools that's missing the tools.
Uh, just if you click, uh, checked the tools and the tools come and.
Yeah.
It's on the menu, but we can check.
Uh, did you, uh, insert, uh, this is a, uh, I mean, if you, um, uh, unable to get any comment
from there, uh, then just go menu insert the, uh, this is a very helpful and by that we can, uh,
search, uh, many commands and it's like course drive cause, uh, in that there are so many commands,
design feature, there's so many features associated coffee.
There is a pattern pattern where there are so many commands.
But, uh, insert this is a very, uh, important, uh, uh, options.
If you want to navigate.
Come on.
You just go so.
Hmm.
Uh, just let me start some.
And this is a tumbling.
Yeah.
Let's drop something and then we click, uh, extortive.
Yeah, just checking this one and then click.
Oh, Skip, finish your sketch finish.
Gansett.
Uh, sketch.
By clicking there, the sketch, just like the idea, if you, uh, okay.
And just make a circle here.
Hmm.
But when he.
Would it be?
Yeah, this is a partner we get.
If you want if you want to edit.
The feature you can, uh, buy that option, you can edit if you want to, uh, if you can remove text
tool of this, uh, you just click on there.
The command is edited and also that if you want to if you don't want to exclude this one, you can take
and check that that will be removed if you don't want to.
Uh, if you want to remove this sketch by there and check, you can remove that.
And if you want some editing on there just right, click on there and just edit it.
But then by that you can edit it.
You can, uh, you can change the dimension of it.
Hmm.
If you were on to.
It will be change country and finish the sketch that you can check, uh, our cycliste change and I
will also change.
This is a most important, uh, partner we get.
And.
So.
This is an import and export, if you want to see that model in another form by the export option,
you can convert it in any other form.
It is easily just like user defined feature for exporters like.
Yeah, you can buy that.
You can export it in any other form, like, uh, Assali party, um, uh, uh, eight years and a step
forward.
And by that import you can uh, you can uh open uh any other forms of uh formats file just like a solid
steel file against step file a separate file Curtius file for file files just like that.
Uh yes.
Uh, I say you by clicking dorkin it will be closed.
Uh, no exit.
So.
We already discussed about what environment the more a future based environment in which you can create
solid models, two-dimensional, sketching, advanced modeling tools and.
We already see the sketches by demonstrating on the.
And you can reopen the next of three.
Just wait a minute.
It will be open.
Just check, this is a anex.
Siemens, PLM software Anex.
Yeah, you're soaking.
By clicking on the New Newport.
Model and then OK.
I already discussed about this is a sketcher in that we can check various sketch lines, uh, to these
sketches, uh.
And this is a features by at the time, you can, uh, make, uh, clean.
Multiple planes, uh, a number of planes you can enter and things, then things is ready if you want
to just, uh, in the distance, the church in the distance and then walk.
The plane is ready.
You can design several designs from there, sketching on there.
This is extrude.
Come on.
I already discussed about that for making a model to do it through.
This is, uh, will come on by taking we can make a model with, uh, to build uh the world model by
uh uh uh center line, uh, at uh uh this is a permanent feature if you want the, uh, same model,
same, uh, profile on, uh, model, you can perform that that we discuss about that, uh, to draw.
That we won't make this.
And if you want to deposit.
Just the Dr..
Yeah, check it, do the wall.
OK.
If you want better.
So that future exclusive, I got the.
And, uh, which distance?
Oh, 15.
Uh.
150, 180 is definitely and if you count back on, you can increase the number of entities.
OK, let's check.
You can see there are 10 US experts are looking at the distance of 180.
Mm.
It is a by move.
Come on.
This is absurd.
There are so many.
Come on.
We will learn in that lecture so that we close.
And uh, in my next lecture I would learn from the.
Schedule, we will discuss all about that, come on, OK, thank you.