Hello, friends.
Let me start the installation process, and that's OK.
So I already downloaded the software and the all the setups and all the files, uh, I saved in that
folder.
Its name is an expert installation of the clicking that we called these files.
I'm refreshing it, so for the installation, you need to click on and extra one 120 and of course only
down.
Look, get the application, the setup, click on their.
So you get this interface.
This takes some time for computerizing your space that fulfilled or not.
So just wait.
It takes.
I just relax and sit back and wait for a response.
I think it's completed and then go next and select, modify.
No need to slack in these and then click on the next.
This is the.
Uh, all the features that you got of that installation, these fight the next.
Uh, the setup is, uh, already selected.
And so in that C program file and see when the next twelve point zero and license, just check, uh,
the, uh, d the match with your next door name just by clicking on the.
This PC, we can right click and then go to property.
And then the device name and its name will be Neupogen seem equal to seven eight zero at their your
device name.
OK, uh automatically said it got your PC's name if it's not good.
Uh, because name you can change.
Uh, because I already installed the software.
That's why it, uh not uh giving me an option for editing.
Then what if you install first time you will get these uh, the option of changing the name of the device,
uh, the two seven eight zero zero under this comment.
What you need to change these, uh, this, uh, the whole kit and click on install.
After clicking on the.
You got this into this.
It's computer computing space equipment, again, where things don't.
OK.
It's going long.
I, uh, if it's computer, do you need to click on next, next, next and after it's, uh, when,
uh, after the, uh, the completion of that, you get finished option and then you can, uh, when
if you click on finish, then it's automatically, uh, closed this option.
So I am going to cancel this because, uh, it's removing some files because I already install an X.
Uh, so for saving time I can sell it and go.
Forward for explaining they want to cancel the installation is.
Oh, chillis interrupted.
Uh, after the, uh, next next, uh, clicking on that's next, next, uh, you will get two to three
pop ups.
Uh, you will get these poppers or finishing, uh, you will get the, uh, the system has not been
modified to the program at all.
But you got, uh, down there, uh, a store completely successful, start completely.
And then I'm going to finish and then, uh, go to the next 12.
And one soldier scored an extra point zero and copied these file.
With these five.
And faced for the first go to see trial program file and then click on.
Simians.
Click on the next 12 point zero and all the files that you copy, paste your.
The police, the fight continue.
Yeah, you all the same.
And then what do these soldiers call, oh, I go God forward.
Movies and installation and installation launch.
Dogs.
So it's quiet, this is a vendor license and this is a license, you need to double click on the.
This is a spear them licensable.
Just click on the.
These click okay.
And next, next.
I don't know why this automatically close.
And then click on GET.
And.
Schuster's dolefully.
Next.
Okay, there's sort of doctor that understands what's even more licenser is what we're learning on the
system.
So it means your license is.
The.
To we get to the next.
S. minister pointed out no one there.
After the installation, please restart the system because you can fix some errors.
So our software is over.
Let's check.
Then OK.
Because, uh, um, not to restart the system that way is to lacking.
So the your next, uh, is open and now it's ready to use and you can
draw and design a model, so I'm going to end this session.