Hello, Sergeant, let's start our first lesson on Popken Modelling's.
And today, we learn on the techniques, fundamentals of the two dimensional sketch, this part called
the method and comments to create a sketch used in the part modeling environment.
The comment and the methods are discussed in the context to the part modeling enlightenment in.
You can create a sketch in a two environment, part in the sketch task environment.
You will learn to create sketch in the environment environments.
In any case, you create a rough sketch and then apply the dimensions and constraints that define its
shape and size.
Dimension dimensions define the length, size and angle of the sketch element where the constraints
define the relation between the sketch and element.
In this topic, we will sketching in the part and sketching in the task environment, using the constraints
that emissions control the shape and size of the sketch, learn, sketch and comments, then learn comments
and options that help us sketch, create a sketch easily.
So let's start in order to the in order to sketch, select the new file.
And model.
We will create firstly simple models, so here we can define the name of your project.
For example, the sketch.
Techniques then from the heat from here, you can define the follower to want to save your project.
It will.
I will.
I will remain the same and press, OK?
Creating an export environment is very easy.
So in order to create the scale, you have to activate the sketch comment from here top left sketch
common and to find the plan on which you want to create the sketch.
So sketch.
And define the plan where you want to draw the scale.
For example, seaplanes, let's define this plan and press.
OK.
Now we can start drawing shapes on the selected plane.
Certainly we will learn through comics and provides you with a set of comments to create a sketch.
These comments are located on the dialogue sketch.
Then out of the home, reburn from the home reburn here, the direct sketch artist Colman's.
So if you expand, this one will see all the documents sketch.
First we will learn profile comment this one profile.
This is the most commonly used to comment while creating this sketch to activate the disgorgement,
click the whole dialogue sketch, then profile on the label.
Activate the profile as you move the pointer in the graphic view as you move this year.
If you move the point on the graphics window, you will notice that the box is attached to it.
It displays X and Y coordinate of the pointer.
So X and Y coordinates to create the line, click in the graphic window.
Click.
Right, left, left, mouse, move the pointer and click again, move the pointer and click again,
line is created after clicking for the second time.
You see, you can see that the end point is at the end and as a line segment is created, so another
line is created there.
It could be horizontal or inclined or vertical and horizontal or incline it segment is created.
This is the convenient way to create the chain of lines.
Continue to add more lines.
Say you can right click.
OK, continue like this.
Like this.
Contini can.
Draw lines, same as you can, right, click in the graphic window and click OK, or press escape the
keyboard looking right click and press in order to escape from the profile comment.
If you want to add and the changes, you will notice that the profile comment is still active.
If you notice here, profile.
Coleman is still active.
You can create another channel of the line segment or press escape to deactivate this comment so you
can create in a chain of lines, or if you press the escape, we will activate the profile.
So we activate the profile command.
The profile Coleman can also be used to draw arcs continues with the lines, so let's click the profile
one more time here.
If you see the address to our comment on the profile people, so click to Art, then you can create
ARC.
The video profile, Coleman.
So it is the two way of using the profile, you can draw the line straight line, horizontal or vertical
or incline Islam, or you can draw arc in the profile, too.
So you will deactivate the profile comment to delete the lines to this lines, create lines, select
it and press the delete keyboard.
So select it and please delete keyboard to select the more than one line.
Click one of the lines samant.
The lines will be highlighted.
You can also select multiple lines by the dragging and box from the left to right so that I can bolt
from the left to write more lines is highlighted, selected and press delete.
So also delete this out.
So.
This is about the argument.
Next.
Sketch comment is a rectangle.
This creates a rectangle using the frame it is first one is a rectangle by two points and rectangle
from the center and the rectangle by the three points.
So here we will see rectangle comment.
So select a rectangle and you will see three options estimation of rectangle by two points, rectangle
by the three points and rectangle from the center.
Let's see all of them step by step.
Rectangle by two points, first one, this method creates a rectangle defining its start and dimensions.
So.
On the rectangle dialogue, click the rectangle by two, pointing to it and then click to define the
start point and start point of the rectangle and define the end point of the rectangle.
So start point of the rectangle and end point of the rectangle.
First point and the second point is for your starting and ending point or two rectangles created.
Next is a rectangle by the three points.
This one, this method creates an incline of the rectangle.
The first two points define the reach and inclination angle of the rectangle.
The third point defines its Saheed so we can create the inclined rectangle by this method.
So first points define the first two boys, define its reach and inclination first and second and its
third point define its.
So the first point.
Second point and third point.
Inclan rectangle is created.
Also we can create.
Straight acting like this.
Using this method.
Next up, to create a rectangle with a rectangle from center.
This method creates a rectangle by defining the three points central to rectangle, first point and
the midpoint and last point is the end point of the head.
So activate that rectangle from the center activated.
Then we will specify the center of the rectangle, move the pointer and click to define the width and
orientation angle of the rectangle.
Then move the pointer and collect to define the heat of the rectangle.
So we will define the center, move the pointer to define the orientation angle and the the and the
width of the rectangle.
Then the click again and move to define the height of the rectangle.
The same as that is the same as the rectangle by three points.
We can define the rectangle using this method into an.
Lieutenant.
That's OK, just press the escape in order to activate the rectangle.
Colman's So this is the Meadow's have to create rectangles using the three points, you can create a
rectangle, three rectangles or Inclan rectangles if you wish to select the rectangles.
Press the delete, select, isolate this one and select the last one.
So.
This is about how to create rectangles, so next common is a circle here next to the circle, Coleman
can be created using the two methods.
So activate the circle.
Gaumont circle can be created by the two methods.
First is the circle by the three points and circle by the three points and circle by the center.
So circle by the center or diameter.
This this is the most common way to rob the circle.
Activate the circle command.
So activate the circle by the center.
Quick to define the center of the point, the center of the circle, so click and click again to define
the diameter of the circle, could drag into the house and define the diameter.
So circle by the center in diameter is created.
First point, Centrepoint, and here that is all they omitted is divine, next method of to create the
circle is a circle by the same point.
This does create a circle by using the three points.
So activate the circle by the three points here activated.
Then select the three points from the graphic Zendo, you can also select the existing points from the
Dumitru.
This is the first two points define the location of the circle.
And so point defines each day and the first.
Second defines its location.
Third point defines it today, and so this is the circle created by the three points method.
So circles are created by the press, the escape in order to activate the circle, Coman select the
circles one by one and delete.
So this one and now the next step is to learn Mark Coleman from the sketch techniques.
So art is here.
The dismantled.
The art method creates the art using the two methods, first one.
So first, what are the three points?
And second ones are the center.
These are the three points.
This matters create an art defining its starting ending in ready.
So let's activate the art with this three points.
It's activated then.
Then click to define the start point of the arc.
So this is the start point of the arc, click again to define end point.
This is the end point.
And after defining the start and end point of the arc, you need to define the size and position of
the arc, move the pointer and click to define the radius and position of the or move the pointer to
define the position and radius.
So art is created with the sequence.
First point is here.
Second point is here and third point is here.
So next e arc with the center.
This method creates the arc defining its center start and end point.
So.
Activate the center part is activated.
Click to define the center point, central point is define it next to move the pointer and you will
notice that the dotted line it views between the center and the pointer.
So.
The plan is a beautiful.
This line is the radius of the arc, no click click to define the start point of the arc and move the
point.
You will notice that the arc is drawn from the start.
Point one, the arc appears the way you want to define the each end point.
So click and throw up.
So art is created by the serpent.
So this is the two methods, how to create the ark.
Press escape to the activate the argument, so select the first answer first and then delete.
OK, delete it and let him do it.
So next is to this next step is to throw the plug on Coleman.
So if you expand the sketch, cause you will see here the polygon symbol.
This is the sketch techniques to draw up the political discourse and provide a simple way to create
the polygon with any number of sites to activate the polygon here is activated.
So and click in the graphic will look to define the center of the political collegiate center of the
polygon is defined it as you move the pointer away from the center.
You will see the preview of the political look here.
You will see the preview of the polygon to then to change the number of the sides of the public and
just click the number of size boxes on the dial and enter the new number.
Here we have six number of the portable, so we can maybe change the eight and so on pressed enter.
We will see here the political side increased from the six to eight next.
So.
Now you have to define the size of the polygon on the dialect, the size meaning has three options to
define the size of the political here in the size.
You have three options, first one inscribed traduce, second one circumscribed radius and the side
legs, for example, if you select the inscribed radius.
The pointer will be one of the flat side of the polygon, so so if you select a circle slide radius,
for example.
Polygon.
The vertex of the polygon will be attached to the pointer in the window to define the size angle of
the bullet.
You can also define the size and angle of the polygon by entering the values in the radius.
And the rotation box is here.
You can define the radius, for example, the 200.
Precedented and the, for example, 90 degrees, it will become the 90 degrees you see.
Press escaped and the Dileep.
Paulina.
That's that's about the next moment is the Ellipse Coleman.
Here, if you expand the sketch, you will see the Ellipse, this comma creates an ellipse using the
center point and major and minor axis.
So activate the Ellipse activated.
Then click to define the center of the Ellipse, end of dialogue type typing value in major cities and
minorities.
We can hear the type where the and all the major ideas is it and the minorities, for example, certify
it's everything and so on.
Elipse dialogue.
So we will we will type the values in the major and minorities.
You can also drag the track the arrows attached to the Ellipse to define the major and minor ready for
click here.
So Elipse is created.
We can drag and drop in order to define the major and minor radiuses in the Ellipse.
So you can also write the exact values.
On the dialogue, we can also type in type an angle of the ellipse here.
The angle is, for example, you can right here, it's now it was 055.
You see the angle of the Ellipse is 45 degrees.
Press, OK, ellipses created.
So like the Ellipse press delete.
For today, Lessem is the last command is still displaying command.
So here you see, you should expand.
We will see this to display and common this common Christerson will be spelunker using two different
methods through the points and Bayport be spline are non-uniform, which are used to create the smooth
shapes so activated.
We have two methods of creating spline studio, so Saluda points and Bibles, let us see the through
the both.
So.
To it and you can.
Create the best plan course, so you see it like it is created.
And second, we can create by the they are almost the same.
OK, this was created created this is the about the first lesson, how to create the simple object,
simple sketch in an environment from the next lesson, we will see how to put that dimension for this
kind of sketch and how to put the constraints in this kind of sketch and making more complex sketch.
See you next lesson.