Hello, Soudas.
It is the second lesson on the next course on the manufacturing process.
Today, we will learn on how to put dimensions on the existing skills, existing simple skills, and
how to put geometry constraints on this case.
So it is generally considered a good practice to ensure that every skill you create is fully constrained.
And before the creating sold futures, the term for formal constraint means that the sketch has a defined
and shape and size.
You can fully constrain a sketch by using the dimensions and constraints as you create a sketch in.
Some dimensions are added to the sketch elements.
These dimensions are quality driven, driven dimensions, and they do not have any control over the
schedule.
If you want to these dimensions to control the shape and size of the geometry, you have to convert
them into three dimensions.
Three dimensions are also limited because they drive the geometry of the sketch.
You can add driven dimentia to skate by using the rapid dimensions command.
So in this environment, is OpenNet already here?
Plus the sketch and press the plane as usual, every time when you start with the skates, you have
to always design the plan where you want to draw your skate.
Press on this plane is defined.
So in the driven dimensions, the sketch using this sketch, using the rapid dimension, comma.
So here you see the rapid dimensions.
You can use this command to add all type of time is the such as the length, angle and diameter.
This month creates a dimension based on the geometry you select for yourself to damit dimensions of
the circle.
Activate the rapid dimension and then click to the circle.
Next, move the point and click again to the pole position the dimension.
You will notice that the box pops up tiepin well in the box and then press enter to update the dimensions.
So firstly to create the circle with the method of the center.
So create the circle and collected the dimension rapide dimension and click the circle drag and drop
the.
They mission and press.
So here you see dimension is given and we can put rapide dimensions in the driven dimension.
For example, we will type, for example, is one hundred, one hundred and press.
And so the diameter of the circle is change.
This is the how to put the dimension on the circle.
So this is the one would also be can put the dimensions in the rectangle, for example, to drop the
rectangle by the two points.
First point and the second point, rectangle is created to escape in order to to deactivate a rectangle.
So.
Press the rapid dimension, let's move here, then press the legs and press it is the 101 millimeter
so we will change it, for example, 110.
OK, 110 press enter and then.
Heat, for example, 70.
You see, it becomes reality and press, and so it is hard to use the rapid definition.
It is hard to use the rapid dimensions of press escape.
Also, we can put the dimensions here, the lines.
For example, draw the line that I broad and press again, so.
Press the rapid dimension and press the line.
It is 116 and we would like to that length of the this line is 200 precedent and it will become a 200.
And close that one.
So this is the method of to use the rapid dimension.
So there is also several methods to to put a dimension, for example, in a dimension angle of dimensions
and vertical dimensions for the lines.
For example, let's firstly delete this sketch.
Selectable and.
For example, the imagination, for example, allows you to create the very start of the Lynam dimension
selector, for example, saucily draw a line horizontal line.
Then.
From the rapid demolition, it ends here, here you see the methods.
If you open the methods, you will see the several methods of putting them a horizontal and vertical
dimension to tentacle point to point angular dimensions rather than motion.
So, for example, the horizontal dimension put in, for example, 200.
Okay, 50.
If you draw the vertical line, for example, here and select a dimension, and if you use the horizontal
dimension, this only issue here, horizontal dimension.
This only gives the horizontal dimension of the land line, for example, one them.
And if you change it to the vertical.
This gives you only vertical line, you see.
This also lets do 100 rescues if you drove the.
In CollabNet Line and Selecta, this just this one and make it infrared and you can.
In this case, you you can choose any dereference application of horizontal or vertical or actual length
of the line, for example, actual length is you can put, for example, one hundred fifty this is that
how to use them?
There are several methods of putting the dimensions.
Also the let's to make the one line here two lines is any angle so you can create the angle between
the two.
Lines and dimensions, so so like this one.
So like this one in.
Put the angles, for example, one hundred twenty, so angle speakers, one hundred twenty.
This is the methods of putting the dimensions so.
Let's see one more time, for example.
Horizontal line here, the rapid dilation.
Here, for example, horizontal line only horizontal dimension, because it's constrained here on the
horizontal, for example, one under the gate, it's clear then.
Here, vertical only, we will select vertical land, so it's constrained vertical, so only that if
you move any, any, any kind only shows vertical land.
So.
Go also, that's 100.
You should, Rob.
Line and just click rapid dilation and all and select here, not horizontal, not vertical, just inserted.
Okay, you can.
That you can.
Selecta put the dimensions, actual length of the actual length of the line.
Also the horizontal and vertical that if you move so actual length, you can put, for example, also
the numbers is just.
Numbers are important here.
We can select and delete.
That's about
that's about the dimension.
Let's talk about our constraints in the next environment.
There are some cases there will be the overconsume in its case, for example, through the rectangles
for the beginning.
So when they're creating scales for the solid surface future and X will not allow you to over constrain
the Jum with the term over constraint means adding more dimension than required.
So you will add more dimension than required the following, if you will.
That rectangle shows the constraints scale.
So if you put dimensions here, for example, the one hundred sixty, let's put it to 150 press enter
and.
For example, let's 100 we define it, two sides of directing, it means it is fully constrain it.
Let's do it this once.
OK.
It is the system is to fully consent because two sides are fully defined.
So this is the formal constraint.
So.
I would like to define that diam the diagram of this rectangle.
You will al-ahmed with the red with the updates, cage alarm.
This means that your system.
Is your system is over it, so it means that this that are going out is not required because to say
this is enough to define your record.
So in this case, press, OK, and in order to decrease the OVERCONCENTRATE level, just like this one,
the press this diagonal and convert it to reference press.
This one.
So this becomes the reference line is additional line.
So your system will not become the norm over constrain the system.
So you have to avoid the overconcerned system.
So the alarm of that will constrain.
So this is the how to put the dimensions, let's see simple examples on how to do the damage for the
other elements, for example, the ark.
Let's draw the ark from the center, that center point radius.
And last point.
So if you would like to put rest this for this, outlets selected this art and it is the same twenty
nine point four or four.
And I would like to add one hundred, for example, it will become the ark will become 100 millimetres.
So.
This is how to put a dimension using the epidemic in the US to deal with this next phase of our is our
lecture of today is the geometrical today.
This is also one of the important point of our lesson, because the geometrical phrase is mostly used
to.
Camonte, in this changing environment, drove your skates in the proper geometry constraints allocated,
if you look here, the more if you open, the more you will see here the geometric constraints.
So.
Collect the geometry concerns and you see here several type of the geometrical strains, it is the kaleena
considers the equal areas or parallel vertical and so on, we will see all of them step by step.
So geometrical strains are used to control the shape of the drawing by establishing a relationship between
the sketch and element.
These geometric strains can be applied using geometric constraints.
Colman's here then from the more open, the more so.
First step of the geometric constraints is the coincident to this constraint connects to a point with
another point.
Select the point to be made consistent and equal on the context to the selected points will be connected.
So in order to activate the.
The consensus let's to draw.
To.
Lines, two lines, so let's throw one vertical line and one horizontal line, so I would like to connect
this point, this point.
So then open the geometry constraints.
That's the coincidence.
That creates constraints.
Two or more verticals on the one point.
On the one points.
This one in here.
You have to select two points that select the object to consider.
So like this one and select this one.
This two points is constrained, OK, to become coincident.
This is the way of the two making the coincident.
Coincident, the.
To become the conscience of next is to this issue, open the door to constrain is the point on the court.
This one point on the court, this constraint makes a vertex of point to be on one line code for circle.
Let's draw the same as two.
Lines here, horizontal and vertical, open the.
Judgmental coastland common so.
So select a core end point and click the point on the Corzo, select these.
And select this, this will become in one line.
So this is the method of to use the metal constraint point on the court so close and let's delete.
Oh, to continue with the next Dumitru constant first Lytro, that's any.
Right, let's put the definition.
Let's eat.
OK, let's incline at.
The nation, let's put the Dymaxion.
Or read actual dimension, for example, one hundred.
One hundred and open, the geometrical next is the genetic code is tangent, this constraint makes our
circle of time tangent to another ARKOS circle so it becomes the tangent.
So select this one so that the line of love for the first line and for that they can select the circle.
So it will become clear the tangent, OK, circle and the line become.
And this is the very useful comments in the real cases.
OK.
Next, these.
That's the.
Next next, we stroll through, for example, lines, so any line you can, for example, put the dimensionless
using the rapid dimension.
The actual dementia, for example, one hundred fifty, you can move that I mentioned on the set for
the second is, for example, hundred.
So open Jimm constraint and next next constraint is Perryville for selected Perello selected this one
first the line for the second, select this one and they will become very see here the symbol of the
parallelism.
That means that these two lines are parallel to each other.
This is the method of making that system.
Next is.
Concentric.
So how is the how does constantly constrain this work in order to do this?
Let's make Drew.
Two circles, for example, this circle.
OK, let's remember this circle cannot rule.
OK, let's put the dimensions of this circle.
For example, 50 mm, open the geometric restraint and here you will see concentric functions, this
constraint makes the center of the art circle or ellipse coincident.
They mean they will make the center of the Arctic Circle and Ellipse coincidence.
So select this one for the select for the first object selected this circle for the second object.
Select this one.
So the circle of the centers will become in the one point it means its concentric.
So.
OK, it's clear next, dramatic.
Constraint is horizontal.
Let's do.
One.
In line at line, let's put dimension folder, that actual dimensionless, the one hundred twenty,
if you see it is in line and time line at line.
Let's open geometrical straight.
And here you will see the horizontal constraint.
That means if you select this one in, select this Inclan line, it will become horizontal, OK?
As well as you can make the vertical atlas.
Drew.
Did I mention one hundred fifty?
Close.
Geometrical strains.
And you see here, vertical, select vertical and select this incline that it will become vertical line.
OK, this is how to make that and horizontal plan also we'll see how it length geometrical constant
here, equal length.
So in order to make the equivalence, let's throw one.
Line, for example, this line.
And this line get.
You have not to put the dimension for in this kind, of course, because if you put the dimension and
they use the equal length constraint, it will be over constraint of function because you put putting
the dimension.
It's also one of the longest making the constants or two constraints will become lead to the system
over constraint.
And so geometry constraint here, equal length.
This selected this one in from here to this one.
This will become an equal.
And so this symbol represented this and this one is an equal length.
So for example, the.
So that would like to
check the check, the length is one hundred thirty.
And this is also on hand.
So it means that it's all because all of this one is equal, this one.
OK, let's.
Let's deal with this one.
So this is how to make equal length.
Also, there is exist the equal radius, for example, select circle and open the geometry constraints
and make, for example, equal areas here and selected this one for the second.
Select this one.
It will become equal.
Ready for this one.
It's 80.
Millimeters in diameter issues.
Check this one until it becomes 18.
This is it.
See, it shows that the system is our concern because we already defined that this reddish diameter
already is equal to this.
So that's why it's not enough.
It's not necessary to show the diameter for this sort of because it is is saying this one, this symbol
you see here, symbol and this symbol, this shows that they are equal radius.
So next is.
Let's throw this.
And the plot, for example, the demolition 100 is in Indonesia and the one.
And open the geometric constraints here, we see the perpendicular coastline, so.
I would like to make Papanikolaou of this light that this was also like this one and this one, this
will become available in the 90 degrees.
So let's move and the next constrains in order to make the next course.
Let's do one simple.
Object to rectangle, let's.
Put the dimensions of the rectangle, so that's the main one hundred eighty and the what is the one
hundred?
Let's make it one under ten press enter.
So then draw one small circle here.
Let's put the dimension for it.
For example, 20.
So let's open the door to the groceries and you see here the midpoint, that means this I would like
to make the midpoint.
This circle under this oak selected this one and select this one, so this circle will become in the
middle or midpoint of this line, so it is in it if it is in one hundred.
So it is in a distance of the 90 millimeters.
If you check the dimension now, it will be over constrained.
So all I can say is 90 because it's over consent, because I already define it.
That is illimitable.
So it's not necessary to put a dimension here because it's already defined that it's in the 90 millimeters
that it's clear.
So.
In order to continue the other constraint, let's let's firstly draw on simple.
Object with the using the profile command, so it's just a simple object.
Let's the forcedly OK.
Press asking that I would like to make the call on this line with this line, so open the geometry constraints
here, you will see Kalinin constraints like this one and select firstly this one.
And this will become decreased until this is like this one and it will become the linear two lines.
It's also most commonly used threes in the real application.
OK, that's all about to have to put dimensions and geometry constraints for the simple sketch.
From the next time we will learn how to make the patterns symmetrical and mirrors more complicated sketch
techniques, then we will make excess on sketch thickness, two dimensional sketch.
So that's all for today.
Thank you very much and see you on the next lesson.