Hello, students.
This is the third lesson on come from the manufacturing process course today in this lesson we learned.
For the.
Comments on the techniques making that helps to make more complicated objects in the two dimensional
environment.
Firstly, let's.
So that is cage, as usual, select plane and press, OK?
So first come for the today is asymmetric comment, this comment makes two objects symmetric about the
line.
The object will have the same size, position and orientation about the line to activate the comment
from the ribbon.
Barred from the ribbon, click the home.
Click the home dedicate.
Direc and.
That and more here more and here you see that makes a military function and a click that makes metric.
So this is the hub to open the big synthetic function.
From there, you will open from the more you see in the next method.
So in order to use this command, let's draw firstly a simple object, this rectangle.
Let's put the rectangle rapid dimensions, for example.
Two hundred
and.
For example, one hundred.
And then.
Let's make semantics or use the more mixed method, so for the here.
Select the object, let's select this line and for the second object to this, select this one.
So for the center line, for the center, like select this y axis.
So this line and this line, you see become symmetric.
So this is seen Monceau.
And press this one, and I would like to make certain this and this side of the rectangle selected this
one.
You see the direction you selected this one for the central line, in this case, Selek.
Why so this and this becomes cemented as well, D-line sides also see how this city function is used.
Let's see one example, unsymmetrical to McSmith with the complex.
She.
Let's firstly delete the size of the rectangle.
Well, then let's activate the profile comment here.
Profile and Andrew.
This kind of shape.
An activist here, OK, in order to continue to ask, so you see his continued and grow.
Line and activate, fill in and.
Roll this one.
So press escape, this is the drone, that's the make the one.
One more thing from here, geometrical screen.
And you see here the tangent make tangent, this one and this one.
This will become the tangent, OK?
And press close.
So I would like to make schematic of this line in this line, so.
More makes symmetric, this line and this line along this central line, sorry.
Let's make forcedly delete this one and throw.
Horizontal line, vertical line.
Dylan.
This one.
In this one and select symmetric function similar to this one.
For the second group, this one alone central, and so this is it will become cemented.
Also, you can make the symmetry of this arc.
So Selecter makes symmetric, selected this arc and the celebrities are select the center line.
So the arcs also will become symmetric along the Y axis.
So you can use this symmetric function for the complex shapes and common command user in the for further
comminuted is the reconvert to reference convert to reference Koeman disgorgement.
And that's the sketch element into a reference element.
Reference element support you to create a sketch of desired shape and size to convert the sketch element.
Firstly, let's throw in its vertical line.
So to convert this line to the reference element, click it, click it.
That's to just click the line and you will get this kind of functions.
So from here, just convey to the essence that the selected convert to reference on the contextual toolbar,
you can also convert it back to the sketch element by clicking it and select and convert to equity.
So I will convert it to the reference unit becomes Deshotel and also just click it and will convert
to active can also convert it to the active line.
So this is the one of the most commonly used technique in the sketch.
So convert to reference and make SM.
So let's delete all of them.
So next year, if you open the.
Drove comments, as we learned in the first lesson, we remain at some functions here.
We will today see this function.
So suspension.
We will learn today from this bar is to make feel.
So if you hear you see here, there is the field function.
So this common around the sharp corner created by the intersection of the two lines are circles and
rectangles or polygon vertical.
So to activate this, please press this one.
This is activated.
So this is the Sheeler's function.
And let's throw one simple example.
So, for example, let's throw rectangle.
And put the dimensions for the rectangle, for example, to handle.
And one hundred ten for them, just numbers so you can drag and drop the dimensions, so activators
here to seal it so and select.
This side and this says, you should drop the mouse, you see it is becoming a shield and there is shown
that it is not safe to remain insistent press enter.
So you see the side of the sharp side of the rectangle becomes the round.
So also, for example, you can do the same in this.
For example, make it, for example, to it.
You can change it to the two.
And you see here is.
This is.
That is the come to.
The same you can do for the other side's.
Next comment is making Chancer.
This common replace the sharp corner with Anglet line to activate these Khaliq.
General function, and for example, you can for example, it is the two types of the making, the chopper,
that's the symmetric and asymmetrical, for example, in the symmetric, let's say like this line that
Gollan and this horizontal that you shoot Rajendran, it allows that chaffer to be resolved.
The distance is year 20.
So let's press enter.
It will become symmetric from the two sides.
20 from the seaside and 20 from the decide, so the using the chancer you can make assimilative.
So let's see in this example, selected this site, select and decide if you move.
You see it's becoming a similar thing.
You can see here change the values.
For example, one side is 20 and one side is 30.
So if you see here is a symmetric chapter here from the 20 in here from the sautee.
In this case, it is symmetric, but the same from the both sides went into it.
This is the two methods of how to construct the chancer on the sharp edge of the scales.
Let's delete this, and I think it's clear how to use the transfer function here and see the function.
In order to continue the next comment, let's draw one simple.
Using the profile.
Let's make open this site, issue one, if you can put the dimensions here, for example, the 60.
We can put here, we can remain is a 100 certified for this site, let's make it one hundred.
They said, let's make two hundred twenty and let's make for this size also the same one, two hundred
and five in let's say I mean, also this side, you see so.
Here.
You see quick extend comment, so this comment, if you click here, select the is appearance, if I
would like to continue this OpenNet phase to connect the dots where the horizontal issue, I will select
this one.
You see, the red line is a.
It means that this line is quick extended to the nearest one.
So that's the disease that could extend it to the northeast, to the northeast, to the northeast.
For example, if it is.
Open line, if you select a quick extend and issue, select the issues you wish you would like to select
this one, it's not selected because there is no new element to extend this line.
For example, if I draw this line, that horizontal line in select quick extend, if I say like this
one, it will extend it to the northeast.
You see here the northeast element.
So to the method of use, quick extend common function.
So let's delete all of them.
So.
OK, let's do it next function is QuickTrip moment in order to continue the QuickTrip here, it is also
very useful function, very useful comment, and we'll see how these kind of functions is usable in
the real practice exercises.
So in order to understand this method, let's draw firstly.
Rectangle.
But the dimensions, for example, 250, then 120 for the heat.
So then let's draw the circle in the corner of the.
Corner of the rectangle with the diameter, for example.
One hand so quick trim is use it when so I would like to cut all these elements, these element and
these are small elements on the skin sketch, so quick to select the quick turn.
And I would select where I would like to cut off.
So select this part of the sketch that is cut, cut also you see and this part also if you select this
one, this is cut.
So this is the how quick trim is.
This is a very useful element because in the complex, when you throw a lot of complexity, for example,
if you would like to draw a rectangle, for example, with the arcs here.
So in the arc, in the three points you see and you have to remove this part, and if you would if you
didn't remove this part, this element couldn't be featured at the solid part.
So you have to remove this part in order to extrude this.
So this is very useful element to remove.
So delete all of them.
Next e-mail, Cordner in order to make Kornel, let's throw one.
Line one, the arc and let's throw.
This kind of scam, so make on the I think they may also select this one and select this one, you will
make the corner between the arc and
between Arc and light.
So next comment, if she opened this year here, she also said, quote, This is also very useful comment.
Let's activate all set calls here.
Also in your selected quote, if you select the discourse, you see it will become Alstott so you can
set the distance of the and also by dragging dropping the that this is dropping this.
Also, you can also manually put the dimension of the soul to become far from certain millimeters was
the offset of this from on destruction?
Also, you can change direction here in this states and you see inside.
Also, you can make the sematic, if you like, here, sematic, you see from the two sides, from the
this and from the inside side.
So there is several options to make it offset.
So let's close it and let's make one reference line here.
Reference line here convert to this reference, and the next function is make a.
Here you see they're not here to make me.
So like this one, I would like to mirror or copy of this sketch.
Along the decent line on this, so select a sketch that I would like to make the tomorrow and select
the central line here and you see this sketch is mirrored along this center line on this address.
I think it is very easy and very useful comment.
So let's select all of this sketch and press delete.
And as one of the important sketch, common is the pattern comment.
It can be circular pattern, common or linear.
So let's firstly draw a rectangle here.
Let's put the dimentia, for example, let's make it 400, 500.
And the two hundred fifty, Andrew.
Small circle with the diameter 40, for example, and you can define the, for example, distance from
the size of the rectangle, for example, it is making 50.
And let me make it also so we located this circle, and I would like to make pattern of this circle
along this line and this line, so.
Expand, make better, but don't function is activated.
You see, there is two options, llena and circle.
Let's first be Delina.
So in this case, in the in the selected course that you have to select the school, which you would
like to make the pattern like this one.
And then here you have to select the direction along these lines so that action.
And here you see a number of the Celui, which equals how many Circo would like to let's make it five.
And here you select.
That's the distance.
Like let's make it so, for example, you can make bigger.
Or more be begin, for example, let's make one hundred.
So you see five, one, two, three, four, five, and the distance between these one hundred, all
of them, then you can use the second direction to activate the second direction and select a leaner
object.
So.
The and the.
Linear direction selected this one.
So make it also, for example, fall in the distance east, for example.
Let me eat that.
Let's see closely and it is in an upward direction and you can reverse directions will become downward.
So you see no that.
Make it three.
You see here, circles are a pair, if you upset the press, OK, you see it is linearly patterned circles.
It's very easy.
You will not draw one by one or the circles just to make light of circles in a linear way.
So.
So like this one in lead, let's throw one circle here, I will show the how to make a circular pattern,
so let's make dimentia for this.
Let me make it six hundred and throw the circle.
With the one hundred and the from here, activate the pattern function, and here you have to change
it circle and then select this one specified point.
It's the center of the arc.
And you see here, though, you can change it to the six and the angle, for example, 60 C angle,
but this creating the circle six circles and the distance of the angle between each of these 60 degrees.
Trescothick.
This is.
Overall, over lesson for the today and from the next lessons will make practices on the common and
all the functions that can be learned in the C lessons.
And after the exercises, we will learn how to extrude and how to obtain the solid.
And the rules have to rely on solid functions c on the next lessons.
Woombye.