Hello, Susan.
Let's start the first exercise on the techniques tutorials, so.
Let's open New Nixonland new file.
In the modeling phase, that's defined a name as part one and say this project on the desktop.
OK, and looking.
First, we withdraw this project so we can start as you want, and in this case, let's start to draw
this big circle with the diameter is 300 millimeters.
So Skitch, selected plan and why plane, OK, circle from the barracks to.
And the use circled by the center method, so draw in the axis of origin, draw the circle and press
and put in using some animation.
The diameter was 300, 300 and less, the middle of the -- suicide note, so then the next step,
for example, we can draw firstly the circle and the circle.
So the circle is right.
This is a sixty eight and that is news.
And
so the circle in the same point, in the same axis to circles here.
Drove in circles and put the dimensions.
The radius was 80, 68, and the dead will be 68, multiplied by 10 and the 72 multiplied by two in
the next step, define the distance between this circle and the circle of this circle.
In this circle, the distance was given here for 240 and 220 millimeters.
So distance from here, you.
Two hundred forty and he from here, from here, it was two hundred twenty preschool's, so then the
next step, for example, we can make the arc here is the radius is 40 feet can we can make using the
field function.
In this in this stage, the field is 40, so she and also we can take that there is the you can see
that there is a tangent this all these are in these circles are intelligent.
So we can make the scene here in here for.
Did you see Paul?
We can make the middle of this art, so let's make the mural from the mural function, could let's select
the colors tomorrow.
So we are we are going to make the mural this art and centerline along this x axis.
So we make mirrors on this arc along the center axis.
In this case, when we make the mural, we have to check that the constraint of the tension between
these are in these two circles.
So when he open the geometric constraints.
And tangent, this are in its second object is this circle, so it will become the you see is the tension,
the symbol and with this arc and this circle.
So we made the change.
And so it is obtained at this field.
So next is to make the field here with a radius of 60 using the same functional field.
This one and this one, this was 60.
So in the same year, this one in this one.
Let's make the miracle that the.
Discourse.
Along the centerline of this and the same checked geometrical strains of tangency of this arc in this
circle and this arc with this circle, we made it.
So now in the next step that here we can make the tree move and show that unnecessary part of our scale.
So he he began to move this path and this path using the trim, quick trim function.
Here's the sketch, that sketch Tomasso Trim, don't this, this.
This was peaceful and this was so.
We trimodal to this, so this unnecessary sketch next weekend drove this circle with the diameter is
80.
Circle.
So in the same in the same point of central point of this circle.
So if he if you bring the closer you see it, because the ability to move the center point of circles
in the same point.
So.
In diameter, let's define it and post it.
So next is the control, the small circles in the center here, these three small circles in order to
draw this small circle.
Firstly, we have to define that this circle is the reference circle, additional circles.
So the diameter is one hundred at this one.
One hundred eighty percent, so then the next year, we have to convert it to the reference circle,
so select this one from here, you see convert to the reference, proceed.
It will become this line.
It's the first line then that's defined final once on one line and also convert it to the reference.
That's the reference was in order to help to draw this circle.
So first, let us stop this circle, because it's the way we know that exact point of location here.
Through.
For example, any circle that the diameter is four to eight.
And using the geometric constraint.
Point on the curve, this point on the court for this, then also this point on the court for this.
So it's easy to locate in the exact position that we would like, so.
In order to obtain these two additional additional soldiers, we can use the pattern function from here
but under the curve.
But this circle and the method that's the layout will be sort of will be circular.
So the specified point is this.
Centre of this circle.
So then we can we know that number three also circle with the angle of one hundred twenty, because
if we divide three hundred sixty to the three, we will get one hundred twenty two degree between the
circles is 120 press.
So she.
The.
I did warn me, stay here last.
Gillet.
This part.
They did this one, so let's make the.
Quick extend of this circle, firstly, then draw a line here.
And extend it until the circle here you see extended and make the.
Meerut.
Of this line along the center line of Eakes and its constraints, strains of tangency between this and.
Niece one.
So make the quick trim here.
Then we have to make the art here with the ready 60 field.
60, this this story is in this.
So then we'll get a picture of this for next, throw this part last part of the project, so there is
the radius of 30 to so distance from here.
In here is 60 for less.
First to drove to circles the.
Year in year.
Using the rapper dimension to put the multiplied to diameter and using geometry constraint, put it
like this one.
The disco.
And once he understood we had to do in this war, it was activated.
Look, listen, they did this long distance between this and this circle is 240.
Using the smart decision, put the distance between this and this.
OK, hold on the phone from.
So it's a little different for the celebrities, Diesel are saying this one into this one.
Once again, this distance between this and this tour will be defined at this.
Now, the general here.
Line and creek extend this one, so let's give this one for us.
We don't need this one and extend this one.
So it's extended and they make the Meerut.
This one on the central line, selected Nexus, check the coastline's tangent.
This one, this one is one, they did this one.
OK, OK, OK, quick train of this one and this one.
That's the finish.
Let's say, look, this initial we get.
Our first object.
This is a finish.
No next project is this one.
Guess save the first project.
Let's open a new one.
Model and name, it is that part to.
And the save it to the desktop as well.
OK, that's OK.
OK.
Selective squidge, selective blame, for example, the same as Petraeus X and Y blame, that's.
You can start to draw this path, then this path and so on, so let's draw the circle to this and these
circles.
Select the circle, circle the center, two circles, then let's define the diameter of the circle,
so the only thread is one hundred four, then seconds.
The diameter is one on the twelve.
This one, one hundred four radius multiplied to the cost of the center and the diameter is one hundred
twelve.
Next, these, for example, Ken Rudin, this one is to play this one hundred sixty.
The same axis.
One hundred sixty multiplied by two, because there is fiscal.
And define distance between this and this.
This is the distance is one two hundred twenty and this this is five hundred.
So this distance will be two hundred eighty.
Two hundred eighty millimeters distance, so.
Then can make the ark here with the radius is fifty six the field.
This one.
Can make the same space, more openness about centerline of eagles than we can change.
Check the constraints of those you see this arc.
This one with the circle and this arc within this circle, so they will become the tangent so we can
make to remove this part because you don't need this one in this one.
So dream of this and this one then.
We can.
Draw this line with the.
Langsdorf, 400.
Selecta line here.
So let's draw the vertical line into the lengths or four on the president.
Mom, we have to you you have to do the symmetrical this along with these.
Access to using the more make the symmetric of this point.
And this point along the center line of unsymmetrical.
Next, this.
Drew.
Circle here for the 64.
So go to the scene.
Yes, so go to that dimension.
64 multiplied by two.
Then.
Drew.
Line here and make the quick extend to obtain this line, then we can make the calls, we can make symmetric.
Meerut.
On this one, in this case, we have to check the geometrical scene here, the tendency of this line
into this go.
So next is to draw this length 60 millimeter.
Mm, the same is true to both.
So let's line this on this.
16 millimeters so close.
Now we can make the one thing that in order to obtain the yield.
Chelate, we have to draw firstly here, the line.
OK, firstly, define the distance, it's 220.
This is the distance between this and these.
Two hundred twenty, OK?
Make quick extend this one.
And rode out the radiuses for the shield, this one and this one is for this.
So then we can make the middle of.
And this one, so from here, select the single curve, this one, this one, this one, so alongside
the one on this one.
So it's moved.
The last step is to make the quick trim.
We don't need this, but.
So it was the middle of this white.
OK.
Let's throw here to line.
It is a little bit in California.
So in order to check that geometrical sign, that horizontal this one.
OK, it's only so tangency, this one in the distance, already exists in to just to check, it's correct
or not extend this one so and trim this one in this one.
I think it's finished with the.
Picture the project, that slogan.
Yes.
Finish it makes this.
Is this project so?
In order to do all of this project, you can start to draw these circles.
And that this one and this one as well to continue.
So let's open the news.
Let's first say that this project project to open a new file.
The clip is part three and save it to stop this, okay?
Okay.
Sketch, select the plain, OK?
Let's throw this to this small circle with the diameter is 30 and 50.
The same circle by senator.
To circus.
The diameter is.
30 and 50, OK?
So 10, 50.
Then Kando be to through this is certified, so the amateur is.
70.
Then again, for example, the.
So this was this to ARC's.
So in order to know the ark, that's the.
I draw the line here the length of the distance.
This is 15, so it will be 30.
It's 30 and 80 to mirror, not the mirror symmetric, this point in this point is symmetry along the
x axis.
So it will become symmetrical 50/50, 15, 15.
So the road arch here.
This one in this really.
This one in this.
Fichte in a different drome, this one so then defined the distance.
So now.
Make the middle will this.
Here, the connected call, this one on the central line on this one, so you made the middle, you
see and define the distance this year, 110.
110 and it should be similar.
We have to make it symmetric, this one.
This one's OK.
You made it symmetric.
Makes this through this.
To circle with the ladies is 23.
That is three double, it will be two times.
So that make it mirrored.
Along with this sort of centerline, so let's connect this in the radius of 20 Chaillot this and.
So I
that.
And best, the three story field.
This one in this one, it was the the with the 20 meters.
The.
The same here.
And same here, 20.
So next is to remove a necessary part of this path in this path, so train these.
So.
This.
This one, this one, this.
In order to make also, it needs some steps, steps, the team.
So.
This is.
And we need only this to pass the width of 12, so let's make it.
Firstly, let's do, for example, Kendrew.
Lying in the chair, it's the constraints of horizontal no gates or to let's make a quick extend this
one and make it.
Near along this line and define the distance.
Well.
Make it.
Symmetric, this line, this line in London, this sort of symmetry makes these two.
Clinics in.
And make you feel it in the ready of five.
And so forth, and make it mirrors, you're connected with cables connected to all the keys selected
along the centerline, this one's mirrored in defined distance is 90.
This warm.
This one is from Dean.
There is no need to tell you anything is finish, let me finish, then check.
We should be finished with the third project.
Using the techniques or techniques, that's all for today's lesson and we will see on the next also
on the practice.
After making the practice on the sketch techniques, we continue the extrusion functions as those solid
functions and remove of solid functions.
So thank you very much for your attention.
See you on the Next List.