Hello, Spoon's, let's start our second lesson in practice from cut, cut, cut down modeling on the
manufacturing process cost.
Let's let's start with you, project.
Sees it as after thought number for.
And the folder on the desktop.
OK.
So like this cage and the X and Y plane press, OK?
We will start.
First successful day of this project must first draw the circle, the circle is the diameter is seven
to eight in this circle, the reference circle, then the fifty eight.
Let's let's select a circle in the center.
OK, seven to eight.
Seven to eight percent.
Then friend circle.
Fifty eight percent.
Convert this circle to the reference by selecting, OK, next list to draw.
Also this.
Circle the diameter of 32, it's also referenced circle.
32 percent committed.
To the reference so now is to draw these elements of the project, firstly draw the circle with them,
the 14.
Mr..
Is 14 percent.
Okay, let's try one more vertical line.
That's also the reference line and using the geometry constraint and point on the, quote, selectees.
And like this one, then the center of the circle is the circle, so it's allocated.
Like this up to this element, so.
This element so.
Rope line and make it vertical.
And extend it until the year and make it near.
And the distance it wants to distance.
You six millimeters and they find this at this point in this point below the line, so and trim these
parts so we draw the element inside of the circle.
So now it's to make its pattern of using the circular layout, circular layout, select the curve discourse
to make the pattern specified for the specified points like the center of the circle and the count.
There is six such kind of element with the angle between each of them.
Sixty degrees.
So see your rotated in this way and that of the circle.
The circle with the damage is 20 to.
Twenty two, and now you can hide this reference or course in order to better see our sketch, next
step is to know the element in the two circles with the diameter 12 and 20 to select the circle.
12 percent.
And the same sort of code to the middle and so distance between this and the circles of fifty seven,
so let's defined this distance, this and this.
Fifty seven percent.
Now is only one more line, the circle here with the to 90 closest circle.
The diameter is 90 percent, so now it's to make the ark feel it is a 20 minute diameter stimulator.
So this, this and this 20 millimeters.
And here.
This is 20 now, we can make three of this evidence, so we'll play that part.
The next is to draw these elements here first to draw the circle with the Demitrius 18 in 36.
Eighteen, then four to six different other parameters, distance between this circle and the circle
is 104.
Let's define this.
From the this year.
To hear
104 millimeters.
Then make Mirrool.
With these two circles, this one and this one centerline on the Y axis, so you make the middle distance
between these two circles of 90 millimeters.
So define this one.
This one and this one is 19
Crozet, the year we had after the radius of 40, so we can make the arc, it is 40 minutes to this
one, then it's of or arc with the ladies of 20.
Can make all this in this.
20 percent of.
20.
So now is to make the trip in order to do it on this association.
This one.
This one and this one.
This this was also, I think, this the mistake.
OK, let's say the up to 40, this one and this one is for the 9th.
Correct.
OK, let's take one more time.
This no Sicily lines.
No.
And close it and finish.
So we see our project is finish this project.
Let's continue with the second project.
This one.
Save this one and the file.
Open new file.
Save it as part five.
The same in.
Desktop.
Okay and okay.
So let the sketch playing press OK.
We can start to draw the party starting from here with a diameter of ninety four and the reference diameter
is sixty four.
Ninety four and sixty four this sort of go to the first one.
This is central here, one reference line.
Draw a circle here, the defined diameter is.
12.
And using the geometrical constraint.
Point on the curve, selecta point.
And.
Axis, then again, the point and circle, the same we did on the previous exercise, close it and the
same as previous steps to make it better.
There is a six.
Well, circles button.
Selecta could make button this one.
The method is circular, specify appointee's Centropa circle, it seeks the manifest produce or present.
Drew.
Circle here is the diameter is six to six.
Thirty six percent.
Well, you have to draw this elements in order to do this, let's draw the circle, it's the diameter
is 200.
Circle 100 multiplied by two, then.
Draw two
lines, convert all of them to the reference.
And maybe it's the angle is 30 millimeters.
Delineation between this and this is 30 degrees.
The same man in the middle of this line and this line.
Then we can make to move this part now we obtained these.
So we can.
Convert also this one to the reference one.
So now I'm using the offset, we can obtain these two lines.
The distance is the same here.
Distance is.
12 millimeters here.
If you're there is the opposite function of the core functions like this one, this one in the distance
is 12, rediscuss 12.
And if you make the symmetrical to be in the two sides.
So that's okay.
Now you can make the arc here you see ARC.
The three points, first point.
The second point, and that is to have.
This.
And West Point.
And they can point to both president.
The same will draw the these two lines.
It's the distance is twenty three making offset.
This line is 23.
That's OK, the same arc with the radius of twenty three.
Twenty three percent would be.
Then three city into so.
Close this one and last step is to throw this to.
Part of the elements draw, firstly is the.
Lying and using the geometrical swing, make it vertical so it will come to a close look, we can extend
it, then make it Mirrool.
About the centerline and define the distance between them, it was sort of six.
And make.
The field here, it is, the 10 and nine.
Tim.
And.
So close.
That's to make it easier, OK, to visit.
And make it three.
And make the constraint of tangency.
It in this.
In this world.
It is.
Andrews, one more here, nine percent.
Can then we can make.
The man is finished with close to finish sketch.
Save it.
This is the second project.
Let's continue to search for.
This one.
So it is a good one.
OK, you file.
Part six, Wookey.
Skitch.
So let the plane OK?
Can draw the sketch with the circle 30 millimeters.
30 millimeters.
Then the rest of the circle with the.
The limited release 55
converted to the reference.
The same one one reference line that Kalanchoe to the resonance.
No small circle with the diameter of 10.
But.
Then the same as I did before, geometrical constraint point on the cool to go into this line in the
circle, in this circle close and make it pattern.
This one is circle point and then six degrees of 60 degrees.
Okay, then this one.
Now we draw this circle, the diameter of 80.
80 percent draw this circle 20 and that, too, in the end, 12.
Yes.
12.
Twenty.
OK, let's make geometrical screen coincident.
This with this.
There's the tangency here, that's what let's throw out the tangent constrained.
This one did this one, we get good clinical.
So.
Make it the mirror.
These two on the central axis, on this one, you seem to mirrored and defined a distance.
Is 100.
And.
And then also make the maitre d d d d around existence.
OK, then define the distance from this.
And this is what defines.
Then.
Distinctive it.
We can make it a tangent, this one and this one, and extend this one, OK?
Can make tomorrow we can do all of them one by one, this one and this one.
In this case, we have to make it to check the tendency between this line and this circle the same Mr..
This one and this one on the list exists, and Jada Tangency, this this one in this.
With this one this week.
Through this, actually, the.
The is for the 20.
To do so, let's make it costly and often you see this one.
And this one.
Consider this already exists to try and make.
This one and this one 20.
Make it Miro's.
This one and this one on the school gates mirrored Prestwick crosswind, if you directly press the sea
keyboard from your keyboard, it will open.
The geometry constraint is.
One of the.
Key features of the links.
This one week, last two is this and this and then this one.
We did this one, but as you can see, it's finished with the no, I have to make the dream of the unnecessary
delay this one as well.
Then closing finish now is finished.
You see, we derailed our project.
Last lost project, okay, save this incident for today.
The lesson is our.
And from the next lesson, they will see how to make the exchange and the rules, as I mentioned in
the previous exercise lesson.
See you on the next lesson.
Thank you very much for your attention.